where
どこ
Academia Sinica's February Posture Response Lectures Begin
中央研究院の2月の姿勢対応講義が始まります
We invite Wang Huijun, Vice President to host for us
副社長の王恵軍氏をホストに迎えます。
Good night, fellow friends
おやすみ、仲間たち
I haven't been here to chair this meeting in four years
私はこの会議の議長を務めるためにここに 4 年間来ていません
So now it is returned by the central government
それで今は中央政府によって返還されています
i'm still a little nervous
まだ少し緊張しています
I haven't done this for a long time
長い間これをやっていなかった
but today is very happy
でも今日はとても幸せだった
We have invited Professor Xie Qinghe
謝清河教授をお招きしました
Also our researcher
弊社の研究員でもあります
come here and give us a great talk
ここに来て、素晴らしい話をしてください
His field is of course related to so-called stem cells
彼の分野はもちろんいわゆる幹細胞に関するものです
very tight matter
非常にタイトな問題
So I thought this wonderfully polite
それで私はこれが素晴らしく礼儀正しいと思いました
But before this starts
でも、これが始まる前に
I'm going to make a teaser
ティーザーを作るつもりです
because I always forget
いつも忘れてしまうから
In fact, there will be the next feast of knowledge in March
実際、次の知識の饗宴は 3 月に開催される予定です
It is told by our chief medical doctor
当院の主治医が言います
Causes and consequences of economic inequality in Taiwan
台湾の経済格差の原因と影響
So this is also a topic of great concern to everyone.
したがって、これは誰もが非常に関心のあるテーマでもあります。
So I hope March 29
だから私は3月29日を願っています
Please take part
ぜひご参加ください
Today I would like to introduce Professor Xie Qinghe a little
今日は謝清河教授について少し紹介したいと思います
I haven't known Professor Xie for long.
私は謝教授と長い間知り合いではありませんでした。
but very impressive
しかしとても印象的です
In fact, Professor Xie is also an outstanding cardiologist.
実際、謝教授は優れた心臓専門医でもあります。
So he can actually see a doctor
それで彼は実際に医者に診てもらうことができる
It's just that there is less time now
ただ今は時間が少ないので
he spent a lot of time
彼は多くの時間を費やした
are doing related research now
現在、関連する研究を行っています
Today's topic is also related to the heart
今日も心臓に関する話題です
Dr. Xie and Professor Xie graduated from the Department of Medicine, Kaohsiung Medical College
謝博士と謝教授は高雄医科大学医学部卒業
Go to National Taiwan University after graduation
卒業後は国立台湾大学へ進学
After studying at National Taiwan University as a specialist doctor
私は国立台湾大学で学び、専門医になりました。
Later, it should be on this
後で、これにあるはずです
Went to America in 1990
1990年に渡米
toWashingtonUniversity
ワシントン大学へ
Is that the one in Seattle?
それはシアトルのものですか？
from Seattle
シアトルから
because there is another
他にあるから
at Washington University in Saint Louis
セントルイスのワシントン大学で
Medicine is also good
薬もいいよ
This medical school has learned some of the most advanced research related to stem cells
この医学部は幹細胞に関する最先端の研究を学んできました。
So he is considered a very outstanding researcher in Taiwan.
そのため、彼は台湾では非常に優れた研究者とみなされています。
We're in a national achievement program called the Biotech Medicine Program
私たちはバイオテクノロジー医療プログラムと呼ばれる国家業績プログラムに参加しています
We also set up a team related to stem cells
幹細胞関連チームも設置
He is the leader of the big team, the leader
彼は大きなチームのリーダー、リーダーだ
Therefore, it has made a great contribution to the research related to stem cells in Taiwan.
したがって、台湾における幹細胞関連の研究に多大な貢献を果たしています。
He has also won many awards, including the dismissal of the Ministry of Science and Technology of the National Science Council, etc.
国家科学会議科学技術省の解任など、数々の賞も受賞している。
also published quite a few papers
かなりの数の論文も出版しました
Many of them are in very high-end journals
それらの多くは非常に高級な雑誌に掲載されています
He also has a very special biotechnology fund
彼は非常に特別なバイオテクノロジー基金も持っています
Foundation Award Winners
財団賞受賞者
This foundation seems to give 20 million at a time
この財団は一度に2000万を寄付するようです
or what information
またはどのような情報ですか
25 million
2500万
a lot of money
たくさんのお金
But give them ten years to do the research
しかし、研究をするのに10年を与えてください
So we look forward to having such a good environment
とても良い環境を整えていきたいと思いますので、
He is now a researcher at our biomedical institute
彼は現在、私たちの生物医学研究所の研究員です
Well but also too big
まあ、でも大きすぎる
This is a difficult merger professor
これは難しい合併教授です
So since he's trying to keep his doctor's license
それで彼は医師免許を維持しようとしているので
must go to the hospital to see a doctor
医師の診察を受けるために病院に行かなければなりません
We don't have hospitals in Central Plains
セントラルプレーンズには病院がありません
So he still has to go to National Taiwan University to see a doctor
そのため、彼は医師の診察を受けるためにまだ国立台湾大学に行かなければなりません
Then we are like this age
それから私たちはこの年齢のようです
The most concerned thing is the doctor
一番心配なのは医師です
So we all please the doctor
だから私たちは皆、医者を喜ばせます
because we need their care
私たちは彼らのケアが必要だから
so this
したがって、この
but the doctor
しかし医者は
I think we Taiwanese doctors all know
私たち台湾の医師は皆知っていると思います
are very very busy
とてもとても忙しいです
He is waiting in the morning
彼は朝待っています
A row to more than one hundred
1 行から 100 を超えるまで
I don't know how these doctors see a doctor
この医師たちがどのように医師を診察しているのかわかりません
But he still does state-of-the-art research despite his busy schedule
しかし、彼は忙しいスケジュールにもかかわらず、依然として最先端の研究を行っています
The progress of our kind of medicine
私たちの医療の進歩
does play an important role
重要な役割を果たしています
So we have this anticipation today
今日はこんな期待があります
Come and listen to our Professor Xie tell us about this
ぜひ謝教授の話を聞きに来てください。
The Dream Chasing and Rhapsody of a Physician-Scientist
医師科学者の夢追いと狂想曲
Regeneration
心機再生
we warmly welcome
私たちは温かく歓迎します
Thank you very much for the introduction of the vice president
副社長のご紹介、誠にありがとうございました
Thank you very much all the guests
ゲストの皆様、本当にありがとうございました
Seniors and everyone
先輩もみんなも
Colleagues in our hospital
当院の同僚たち
in relatively cold
比較的寒い中で
And it's raining again
そしてまた雨が降ってきた
come to our events
私たちのイベントに来てください
The vice president politely said he would be nervous
副大統領は緊張すると丁寧に言った
If the deputy dean is nervous
副社長が緊張している場合
Then I'm more nervous, really nervous
そしたらもっと緊張する、本当に緊張する
Because usually if the author in the audience
なぜなら、通常、著者が聴衆の中にいた場合、
They are all like vice-presidents, like secretary-general and academicians.
彼らは皆、副大統領のようなもので、事務総長の学者のようなものです。
Actually, I'm not nervous at all.
実は全然緊張してないんです。
But when I found out that what the audience did was our normal
でも、観客がやっていることは私たちの普通だとわかったとき、
In fact, there are many professors here
実はここには教授がたくさんいます
There are also many of our left and right neighbors
私たちの左と右の隣人もたくさんいます
We even came up to Peng Chang from Taichung and Kaohsiung
台中や高雄からも彭昌まで来ました。
Then I just saw outside
それから私はちょうど外を見ました
There are many students from Jianzhong here
ここには建中からの学生がたくさんいます
I'm most afraid of this kind of speech
こういう発言が一番怖い
Because this kind of speech is usually a little difficult
この種のスピーチは通常少し難しいので、
a little challenging
少し挑戦的な
How can these messages be
これらのメッセージはどのようにして起こり得るのでしょうか
which we want to share with you
私たちがあなたと共有したいのは
There are even some that you can let everyone know
みんなに知らせることができるものもあります
Then we can even promote things together
そうすれば、一緒に物事を推進することもできます
how to convey it
それをどうやって伝えるか
can then cause an interaction
その後相互作用を引き起こす可能性があります
It's actually quite a challenge
実際にはかなりの挑戦です
probably next to a little bit
おそらく少し隣に
I went to the Taichung Science and Technology Museum twice before
台中科学技術館には前に2回行きました
Taichung Science and Technology Museum to give a science and technology speech
台中科学技術館、科学技術講演会を開催
Usually the audience is from 4 years old to 80 years old
聴衆は通常4歳から80歳までです
That challenge is also very high.
その挑戦もまた非常に高いものです。
Later, I really wanted to say that I just brought some toys to
後で、本当はおもちゃを持ってきただけと言いたかったのですが、
go help like this
こうやって助けに行って
So today I want to introduce to you
そこで今日ご紹介したいのは、
Regeneration
心機再生
I remember 16 years ago
16年前のことを思い出します
At that time, the general manager of our former health insurance bureau once
当時、かつて私たちの前保険局長が、
Professor Zhang Hongren
張宏仁教授
He is after resigning from the Health Insurance Bureau
保険局を退職した後です
then go to harvard medical school
その後ハーバード大学医学部に進学
To visit a scholar like this
このような学者を訪問するには
He had one please at that time
その時彼はお願いがありました
backyard rescue over there
そこの裏庭の救助
we eat together
私たちは一緒に食事をします
everyone will chat
誰もがチャットします
He asked me what I was doing
彼は私に何をしているのかと尋ねました
I said I was doing rejuvenation
若返りをしてるって言ってた
He asked me, is it possible to regenerate the mind?
彼は私に、心を再生することは可能なのかと尋ねました。
So I still ask every day to this day
だから私は今でも毎日尋ねます
Is it possible for Xinji to be alive?
果たしてシンジは生きているのか？
It seems like a dream to me
私には夢のようです
Sometimes it's about chasing your dreams
時には夢を追いかけることもある
need to be a little fanatic like this
このように少し熱狂的になる必要があります
This is not madness
これは狂気ではありません
It really means fanatical
それは本当に狂信的な意味です
not arrogant
傲慢ではない
So let's see today if we can
それで、できるなら今日見てみましょう
Let this new accumulation be born this big challenge
新たな積み重ねが生まれよう この大きな挑戦を
can be pushed forward
前に押し出すことができる
may even one day reach one of its goals
いつかその目標の一つを達成できるかもしれない
Thank you very much Vice President just now
副社長、今は本当にありがとうございます
Introduce a little background of mine
私の経歴を少し紹介します
In fact, the main thing I want to share with you is
実際、私が皆さんと共有したい主なことは、
I went to four medical schools after I read it
これを読んでから4つの医学部に行きました
Everyone knows that our medical school in Taiwan takes seven years
台湾の医学部には7年かかることは誰もが知っています
after seven years of medical school
医学部を7年間卒業した後
It took two years to carry out the national duty
国家の義務を遂行するのに2年かかった
Obligation to serve as a soldier
軍人としての義務
five years of residency
5年間の滞在
So another seven years
それでさらに7年
know after seven years
7年後にわかる
So that's what heart surgery is all about.
つまり、心臓手術とはそういうものなのです。
Then come to the United States to study BHD
その後、BHDを学ぶために米国に来ます
do doctoral research
博士の研究をする
Add up exactly seven years
正確に 7 年を合計すると
then come back after
その後戻ってきてください
City University
市立大学
From assistant researcher to associate researcher
研究員補から准研究員へ
Assistant Professor Associate Professor to Professor
助教授 准教授から教授へ
another seven years
あと7年
I think being a professor is actually learning.
教授というのは学ぶことだと思います。
really like a student
本当に学生みたい
So seventy percent and four equal twenty-eight
つまり、70 パーセントと 4 は 28 に相当します
So until now it seems like
それで今までは次のようです
Seems like a student
学生っぽいですね
See if there is any way I can help others like this
このような人たちを助けることができる方法はないか考えてみましょう
good
良い
That's because the topic is a
それは、主題が
How do physician-scientists pursue this dream
医師科学者はこの夢をどのように追求するのか
So I will simply introduce to you
ですので簡単にご紹介させていただきます
i grow up
私は成長します
And the process of chasing dreams like this
こうして夢を追いかける過程も
usually means
通常は意味します
after medical school
医学部卒業後
We now have more and more young
今では若い人も増えてきましたね
friend young schoolboy sister
友人の若い男子生徒の妹
they will want to study and do research
彼らは勉強して研究したいと思うでしょう
In the education of our medical schools in Taiwan
台湾の医学部の教育において
Generally speaking, there is a lack of basic research
一般的に基礎研究が不足している
Abroad is a little different
海外はちょっと違う
so everyone will meet
だからみんなに会えるよ
I'm often asked a question that says
というような質問をよく受けます。
if he is interested in research
彼が研究に興味があるなら
want to go to that doctor
その医者に行きたいです
Do you want to go out after graduating from a college?
大学を卒業したら外に出たいですか？
Or do you go out after your residency?
それとも滞在終了後は外出しますか？
There are pros and cons to each
それぞれに長所と短所があります
Because I left after graduating from college
大学卒業後に辞めたので
Of course younger
もちろん年下ですが
But if you want to come back to Taiwan
でも台湾に戻りたいなら
After you get your Ph.D., you will do research and then come back.
博士号を取得したら、研究して戻ってきます。
already old
もう古い
Becoming a resident doctor may not be enough
研修医になるだけでは不十分かもしれない
So this is something to consider
したがって、これは考慮すべきことです
But if you say that you finished your residency in Taiwan
でも、台湾での滞在を終えたと言うと、
Our cumulative experience is good
私たちの蓄積された経験は良好です
But I haven't been a student for more than ten years since I left
でも、私は辞めてから10年以上学生になっていません。
It's hard work being a student again
学生に戻るのは大変だ
So there are pros and cons to each
ですので、それぞれに長所と短所があります
Just look at each person's situation and make a trade-off
それぞれの人の状況を見て、トレードオフを決めてください
clinical
臨床
So I'm staying as a resident
だから私は住民として滞在します
After that, after getting a specialist
その後専門医の診察を受けてから
Then the next question is to say
それでは次の質問はこう言います
Then I will continue to be an attending physician
これからも主治医を続けます
Or do I chase my dreams
それとも夢を追いかけますか
Go abroad to study for a doctorate
博士号取得のために海外に留学する
Then choose to go out
それから外出することを選択します
because it really is one
それは本当に一つだから
It's been like this since I was a child
子供の頃からそうだった
good
良い
then i choose
それから私は選択します
Seattle
シアトル
Go to Utter Mission Wash's business project to go to this field
このフィールドに移動するには、Utter Mission Wash のビジネス プロジェクトに移動してください
It was so simple when I thought about it
考えてみたらとてもシンプルだった
Because there are actually a lot of implantable medical devices in Xinzang Surgery
新蔵外科には実際に多くの埋め込み型医療機器があるため
You may have heard of artificial escorts
人工護衛について聞いたことがあるかもしれません
Vascular Stent
血管ステント
artificial blood vessels
人工血管
even an artificial heart
人工心臓さえも
And the well-known Yekemo
そして有名なイエケモ
Is Ye Kemo Doctor Ye?
イェはケモドクターイェですか？
Not a doctor surnamed Ye
Yeという名前の医者ではありません
Yekemo is an instrument doing extracorporeal circulation
Yekemoは体外循環を行う器具です
These things are business engineering people
これらはビジネスエンジニアリングの人々です
develop it for clinical use
臨床使用のために開発する
However, although these have been used clinically for decades
ただし、これらは数十年にわたって臨床で使用されてきましたが、
it has some problems
それにはいくつかの問題があります
we hope to make it better
私たちはそれをより良くしたいと願っています
So I wanted to say
だから言いたかったのです
If I can combine engineering to do biomedical research
工学を組み合わせて生物医学研究を行うことができれば
may be helpful
役に立つかもしれない
So this is the time to choose
だから今が選択の時だ
Reasons to study bioengineering
生物工学を学ぶ理由
Then Dr.
それから博士。
When I'm about to get my Ph.D.
博士号を取得しようとしているとき。
But once I came back to National Taiwan University to give a speech
しかし、あるとき私はスピーチをするために国立台湾大学に戻ってきました。
Then my teacher, Professor Lin Fangyi, said
すると私の先生、リン・ファンイー教授が言いました。
do you want to come back
戻ってきますか？
At that time I thought
その時私は思いました
Seems like I learned a little bit by doing research
調べてみたら少しはわかったような気がする
I want to be doing a lot of seniors are
先輩方もたくさんやりたいです
have more experience than me
私よりも経験が豊富です
I just started reading
読み始めたばかりです
After entering the laboratory, I found out that
研究室に入ってわかったのは、
In fact, doing research is not so simple
実際、調査を行うことはそれほど単純ではありません
as if we
まるで私たちが
When Dr. Zhu Yuan wants to learn to be a surgeon
朱源医師が外科医になることを学びたいとき
At the beginning, you must start by learning to brush your hands first.
最初は、まず手を磨くことから始めなければなりません。
Avoid infection by brushing hands
手洗いで感染を防ぐ
Then you start sewing the skin
それから皮膚を縫い始めます
Slowly start cutting the fence
ゆっくりとフェンスを切り始めます
nothing to do with that politics
その政治とは何の関係もない
Start with the simplest operation
最も簡単な操作から始めましょう
Then slowly start to dye until the end like this
このようにゆっくりと最後まで染めていきます
In fact, doing research is like this
実際に研究するとこんな感じです
wait a minute before we continue
続行する前に少し待ってください
So I feel like my PhD is not enough
だから博士号だけでは不十分だと感じている
So I went to Boston
それでボストンに行きました
go do boso research
房総の調査に行く
After doing that, the next question is to say
それを行った後、次の質問は次のようになります。
Do I stay in the U.S. to find a job or do I come back?
仕事を見つけるために米国に残るのか、それとも戻ってくるのか?
Then I chose to come back
それから私は戻ってくることを選びました
good
良い
Why did you go this way?
なぜこちらへ行ったのですか？
In fact, there are still some antecedents and consequences
実際には、まだいくつかの前例と結果があります
there is usually some reason for everything
大抵は何事にも何らかの理由がある
There are some steps into the group
グループに入るにはいくつかのステップがあります
i liked it when i was young
若い頃好きだった
likes to shake
振るのが好き
I like doing things by hand, I don't like studying
手作りするのが好きで、勉強は好きではありません
my wife will find it strange
妻はそれを奇妙に思うだろう
You don't seem to like doing housework that much at home
家で家事をするのがあまり好きではないようです
you would love to move when you were a kid
子供の頃は引っ越しが好きだったでしょう
Actually, I really like to move my hands and feet.
実は私、手や足を動かすのが大好きなんです。
I just like to do things with my hands
私は手を使って何かをするのが好きなだけです
When I was a student
学生の頃
I seem to be doing pretty well in the lab classes.
実験室の授業ではかなりうまくやっているようです。
When it comes time to memorize
暗記する時期が来たら
my grades are not good
私の成績は良くありません
So this is also natural
だからこれも当然のこと
I'm going for surgery
手術に行くつもりです
Will undergo cardiac surgery because
心臓手術を受けることになるので、
In my fourth year of medical school
医学部4年生のとき
One of them went to Chang Gung Hospital as an intern
そのうちの1人は長庚病院でインターンシップに行きました
I saw Professor Zhang Zhaoxiong, the then president of Chang Gung Hospital
当時の長庚病院院長だった張昭雄教授に会いました。
he is undergoing open heart surgery
彼は開胸手術を受けています
i feel amazing
素晴らしいと感じます
i adore him so much
私は彼をとても愛しています
I find it amazing that
すごいと思います
a heart is beating
心臓が鼓動している
Our technology through extracorporeal circulation
当院の体外循環技術
freeze this heart heart paralysis
この心を凍らせて 心臓麻痺
stop the heart
心臓を止める
then open the heart
それから心を開いてください
after getting hands and feet inside
中に手や足を入れた後
This heart problem can be mended
この心の問題は解決できる
Then bring the temperature back up
その後、温度を元に戻します
swim the blood back
血を泳いで返す
heart beats again
心臓がまた鼓動する
and after closing the chest
そして胸を閉じた後
can solve this problem
この問題を解決できる
To me it's really a miraculous thing
私にとってそれは本当に奇跡的なことです
So I thought I'd go with this one
それで、これで行こうと思いました
At that time, it was actually quite large
当時としてはかなり大きかったのですが、
But then I really went this way
でも、本当にこの道に行ったんです
But once you walk in
しかし、一度中に入ると
Until I finished my clinical training at National Taiwan University
国立台湾大学での臨床研修を終えるまで
just feel like saying
言いたいだけ
This life is really wonderful
この人生は本当に素晴らしいです
why
なぜ
Because in fact when I
なぜなら、実際に私が
Every day we have to fight with life
私たちは毎日命と戦わなければなりません
It may be hard for you guys to imagine us
皆さんには私たちのことを想像するのは難しいかもしれません
now everyone is talking
今、みんなが話しています
your working hours
あなたの勤務時間
Then we have to fight for this leisure time and so on.
そして、私たちはこの余暇を得るために戦わなければなりません。
The previous training of Xinjiang Surgery may still be the same now
新疆外科の以前の訓練は今も同じかもしれない
Even Saturdays and Sundays are all counted as holidays
土日も全て休日としてカウントします
The average work day is 16 hours
1日の平均労働時間は16時間です
So it is very common to work continuously for more than 30 hours
そのため、30時間以上連続して働くことも珍しくありません。
It is also common to have to fight with life and death every day
毎日生死との戦いを強いられることも珍しくありません
sometimes we can
時々私たちはできる
save our patients
私たちの患者を救ってください
But sometimes we just can't be that good
でも時々、私たちはそこまで上手になれないことがある
some patients we lose them
何人かの患者を失ってしまう
usually means
通常は意味します
How we lost these patients we probably all know why
私たちがどのようにしてこれらの患者を失ったかはおそらく誰もがその理由を知っているでしょう
So we want to say that we have the opportunity to do better in the future
したがって、私たちは将来的にはより良い成果をあげる機会があると言いたいのです。
But sometimes even if we feel that the patient may not have a chance, he probably
しかし、患者にはチャンスが無いかもしれないと私たちが感じたとしても、おそらく患者は
maybe we can't save him
たぶん私たちは彼を救うことができない
He can ride a mech again
彼はまたメカに乗れるようになる
rescued by us
私たちに救われた
it's weird
それは奇妙だ
Losing patients sometimes we don't know very well
患者を失うことはよく分からないこともあります
sometimes
時々
Rescue the patient We are not so clear why we can save him
患者を救出する なぜ彼を救えるのかはあまり明確ではない
so feel like saying
だから言いたくなる
I am really in awe of life, there are many
私は本当に人生に畏怖の念を抱いています、たくさんあります
what we don't know
私たちが知らないこと
So I'm wondering if there's a way we can learn more about
そこで、もっと詳しく知る方法はないかと考えています。
Because usually the more you know about a thing
なぜなら、通常、物事について知れば知るほど、
Even a scientific study is the same
科学的研究でも同じです
The more you understand why it's what it's mechanism
なぜそうなる仕組みなのか理解すればするほど
then you might have a better chance
そうすればもっと良いチャンスがあるかもしれない
better treatments can be devised to help it
それを助けるためにより良い治療法が考案される可能性がある
it was a simple idea
当時は単純な考えだった
So I went to America
それでアメリカに行ったんです
then i'm in seattle
それから私はシアトルにいる
So everyone, Seattle is on the northwest side of the United States.
皆さん、シアトルはアメリカの北西部にあります。
It’s very close to Taiwan, and you can get there by direct flight from EVA Air.
台湾からとても近いので、エバー航空の直行便で行くことができます。
Then just like when we were young
それから私たちが若かった頃と同じように
Many have the same experience, the same dream
多くの人が同じ経験、同じ夢を持っています
It is said that many campuses in the United States are very beautiful.
アメリカのキャンパスはとても美しいところが多いと言われています。
That's some views of Seattle like this
シアトルの景色はこんな感じ
I want to say everyone come here after dinner
みんな夕食後ここに来てと言いたい
Just to show you some pretty pictures
素敵な写真をお見せするためだけに
So this is the Space Needle, everyone knows it better.
これがスペースニードルです。誰もがよく知っています。
that's mount rainier
それはマウント・レーニアです
this is a national park
ここは国立公園です
That's some scenery of the school
それは学校の風景です
So you can also see cherry blossoms in spring
春には桜も見られるので
In autumn, you can watch the windy night
秋には風が吹く夜を眺めることができます
really can see
本当に見える
But it's beautiful
でも美しいです
In fact, it was quite painful at the beginning of the doctoral program.
実際、博士課程の最初の頃はかなり苦痛でした。
is crying beautifully
美しく泣いています
it's been like this
このようになりました
the first one
最初の1つ
Although I am a graduate of medical school
私は医学部を卒業していますが、
Then also did clinical
その後臨床も行いました
Actually I'm interested in some biomedical stuff
実は生物医学的なことに興味があるのです
It's all old stuff
全部古いやつだよ
Study something every day and keep improving
毎日何かを勉強して改善し続ける
So I haven't attended school in more than ten years
だから私は10年以上学校に通っていません
not that long
そんなに長くない
Haven't attended school for many years
何年も学校に通っていない
Then go back to school all of a sudden
それから突然学校に戻って
It's actually quite hard work
実はかなり大変な作業なんです
Again in a person who doesn't understand much English
またしても英語があまり分からない人にとって
then long gone is
それから遠い昔に
because i used to
私はかつて使っていたので
In our time, it was probably not bad to read and read.
私たちの時代なら、読んで読むのも悪くなかったかもしれません。
Can't hear well
よく聞こえない
I can't write well
うまく書けない
So I was afraid that when I first met a professor in the United States, I would
ですから、アメリカで教授に初めて会ったとき、私はこうなるのではないかと心配していました。
hard to hear
聞き取りにくい
i don't know what he's talking about
彼が何を言っているのか分かりません
He doesn't know what I'm talking about
彼は私が何を言っているのか分かりません
So I took my wife to be an interpreter like this
そこで妻をこうして通訳してもらいました
I still have a clear impression
今でもはっきりとした印象が残っています
But we are pushing our three month old
しかし、私たちは生後3か月を押しています。
we are called boss
私たちはボスと呼ばれています
Then take my wife to be an interpreter like this
じゃあ妻をこんな風に通訳してもらいましょう
to avoid
避けるために
Difficulties in communication start like this
コミュニケーションの難しさはこうして始まる
Then
それから
You still have to take a lot of courses in the first year
1年目はまだたくさんの科目を履修しなければなりません
to fix something like
のようなものを修正するには
Like the five-character class in the Department of Electrical Engineering
電気工学科の5文字の授業みたいに
It's the kind of master's degree in electrical engineering.
電気工学の修士号のようなものです。
Courses currently being taken in doctoral programs
博士課程で履修している科目
I'm ashamed to tell you
恥ずかしくて言えません
Especially the architectural degree here
特に建築学位はここで
When I was in my PhD class last year
去年博士課程にいたとき
I even forgot about the ohm force
オーム力も忘れてた
But he went to take the five-character course in the Department of Electrical Engineering
しかし、彼は電気工学科の5文字コースを受講しました。
So it's a big challenge
だからそれは大きな挑戦だ
Generally business engineering
一般的にビジネスエンジニアリング
Even you have to learn biology
あなたも生物学を学ばなければなりません
Engineering also needs to be learned
エンジニアリングも学ぶ必要がある
So take a bunch of classes
だからたくさん授業を受けてください
Take forty or fifty students
40人か50人の生徒を連れて
Then you have to test a lot of things
それから、たくさんのことをテストする必要があります
before graduation
卒業前に
But after a few years
しかし数年後
Seventy to eighty hours a week
週に70～80時間
time work
アルバイト
twenty to
二十から
Twenty to thirty hours a week
週に20～30時間
results that can be lost at home
自宅では失われる可能性のある結果
i'm lucky
私はラッキーです
I graduated in four years and two months
4年2ヶ月で卒業しました
Then I want to thank my vice
それから私は自分の悪徳に感謝したいと思います
my colleagues
私の同僚
And my wife and my wife's mother look like this
そして妻と妻の母親はこんな感じです
Because of our years in Seattle
シアトルでの長年のおかげで
he went eight times
彼は8回行きました
we have weight
私たちには体重がある
Anyway, if there is weight, pull him to help
とにかく重みがある場合は引っ張って助けてください
and our aunt
そして私たちの叔母
what does my doctoral class do
私の博士課程のクラスは何をしますか
because my teacher is
なぜなら私の先生は
There are many stories about my teacher
先生についての話はたくさんあります
can speak for two hours
2時間話せます
but basically
しかし基本的には
He's also a Harper's surgeon
彼はハーパーズ外科医でもある
But he spends 70% of his time doing research
しかし、彼は時間の 70% を研究に費やしています
So he is actually at the University of Washington, which is independent in West Asia
つまり、彼は実際には西アジアで独立したワシントン大学に在籍しているのです。
He established the entire surgical research system
彼は外科研究システム全体を確立しました
At the time this was very rare
当時これは非常に珍しかった
To this day, few surgeons can do this
今日に至るまで、これができる外科医はほとんどいません
he uses a
彼はを使用します
Use the lungs
利用肺肺
A model of this kind of collar from part of the lungs
この種の首輪の肺の一部のモデル
to experiment
実験する
what experiment
何の実験ですか
Because we do bypass surgery for artificial blood vessels
人工血管のバイパス手術を行っているため
or a stent for blood vessels
または血管用のステント
The problem that will be encountered is the blood vessel
直面する問題は血管です
Although you opened it up
開けてくれたのに
But you artificial things
でも、あなたたちは人工的なもの
foreign body reaction
異物反応
so it's like saying your hand was cut with a knife
つまり手をナイフで切られたと言っているようなものだ
it will heal in the wound
それは傷を癒すだろう
But it heals the wound too much
でもそれは傷を癒しすぎてしまう
So some weird scars
奇妙な傷跡がいくつかあるので、
artificial blood vessel
人工血管
artificial stent placed in blood vessel
血管内に留置された人工ステント
These tissues will also grow
これらの組織も成長します
Finally, the blood vessel is blocked again
最終的には再び血管が詰まる
I came to find out
それを知りに来たんだ
if you can increase
増やすことができれば
When the blood flow of this artificial blood vessel
この人工血管の血流が
then you can
そうすればできます
grow this out
これを成長させて
These tissues inside the artificial blood vessel
人工血管内のこれらの組織
it can be retracted again
再び撤回することができます
So again blood flow can be suggested
したがって、再び血流が示唆される可能性があります
how to do this
これを行う方法
How can this make the blood flow in the blood vessels faster?
これにより、どのようにして血管内の血液の流れが速くなるのでしょうか?
For example, our person
たとえば、私たち人間は、
This is boiling is this part
沸騰しているのはこの部分です
its aorta to the arteries of both feet
大動脈から両足の動脈まで
We connect its two artificial blood vessels
2本の人工血管を接続します
tie it in the middle
真ん中で結びます
So the blood can only go this way
だから血はこの方向にしか行かない
after those two months
その2ヶ月後
It will grow a lot of intima tissue
内膜組織が大量に成長します
At this time, if we are in a remote place
このとき、遠隔地にいる場合は、
Connect its arteries and veins
動脈と静脈を接続します
We all know that normally our arteries go to the vascular
私たちは皆、通常、動脈が血管につながっていることを知っています。
Will it reach the vein?
静脈まで届くのでしょうか？
Then the way I use surgery now
それから、私が今手術を行っている方法は、
connect it directly
直接接続してください
You can let the blood run here and run straight over
ここで血を流して、真っすぐに走ってもいいよ
it's like saying
と言っているようなものです
Originally, there were only three lanes on one side of the expressway.
もともと高速道路は片側3車線しかありませんでした。
You suddenly turn it into a six-lane lane
突然6車線の車線に変えると
The draw will definitely speed up
ドローは確実に加速する
What about the blood flow speeding up?
血流が速くなるとどうなるでしょうか？
It will make the growing tissue shrink again
成長中の組織が再び収縮して​​しまいます
retracted again
また撤回した
then you tie this side up
それからこちら側を結びます
it grows again
また成長する
So its organization is actually scalable.
したがって、その組織は実際には拡張可能です。
ok now here comes the problem
さて、ここで問題が発生します
If there is a patient today
今日患者さんがいたら
His artificial blood vessel is about to become blocked.
彼の人工血管は詰まりかけている。
You say sorry to him
あなたは彼に申し訳ないと言います
I let you open one
一つ開けさせてもらいました
Open a Tokyo Mailou tube surgery
東京マイロウチューブで操作を行う
I can make you shrink back
あなたを萎縮させることができます
Does the patient want you to do it?
患者さんはあなたにそうしてほしいと思っていますか？
Of course not
もちろん違います
probably no one would
おそらく誰もそうしないだろう
So all we have to do is say
だから私たちがしなければならないのはこう言うことだけです
if i could know say
もし私が言うことができたら
This increase in blood flow
この血流の増加
Why do these tissues grow
なぜこれらの組織が成長するのか
retracted words
撤回された言葉
then i can know
そうすれば私は知ることができます
What are the things that I can design drugs for?
医薬品を設計できるのは何ですか?
to do something similar
のようなことをする
Then we can use drugs
それなら麻薬も使えるよ
to simulate the effect of this increased blood flow
この血流増加の影響をシミュレートする
We often do research in this way
私たちはよくこの方法で研究を行います
It's us who bully animals
動物をいじめるのは私たちです
bully them and do some
彼らをいじめたり、何かしたりする
things that happened that they shouldn't have
起こってはいけないことが起こった
learn from it
そこから学ぶ
Thanks also to their students
生徒たちにも感謝
So we can learn to say
それで私たちはこう言うことを学ぶことができます
Maybe how can we diagnose a disease earlier
おそらくどうすれば病気を早期に診断できるでしょうか
how to get better treatment
より良い治療を受ける方法
Then after finishing his Ph.D., he went to Doctorate to be a postdoctoral fellow.
その後、博士号を取得した後、ポスドクとして博士課程に進みました。
We have been to Doctorston
ドクターストンに行ってきました
You can also see this is the view of Temi
これがテミの視点であることもわかります
Halwegen MIT looks like this
ハルウェゲンMITはこんな感じ
But for us
しかし、私たちにとっては
In fact, it is this thing that affects us the most.
実際、私たちに最も影響を与えるのはこのことです。
i hope there are not too many
あまり多くないことを願っています
yangjid fans
ヤンジドファン
me and my wife
私と妻
because the year we went
私たちが行った年だから
Year 2003
2003年
end of 2003
2003年底
year 2004
2004年
All year 2004
2004 年中
He just breaks that Bamber's Cube
彼はそのバンバーズキューブを壊しただけだ
is the curse
呪いです
Won another world championship after 1984
1984年以降も世界選手権で優勝
so i appreciate him
だから私は彼に感謝しています
So my wife and I decided
それで妻と私は決めました
We're going to be Saffron fans for life
私たちは一生サフランのファンであり続けるでしょう
So when I got back, I joked
それで帰ってきたら冗談を言いました
if you are a yangjid fan
あなたがヤンジドファンなら
better not come into my office like this
こんなふうに私のオフィスに来ないほうがいいです
But didn't Wang Jianming go to Yangji later?
しかし、王建明はその後陽吉へ行ったのではないでしょうか？
That's right, when Wang Jianming pitches the ball
そう、王建明が投球するときだ。
yangji can win
ヤンジなら勝てる
When Wang Jianming is not pitching
王建銘が投球していないとき
better not win
勝たないほうがいい
From the time of postdoctoral
ポスドクの頃から
Start to learn how to make stem cells
幹細胞の作り方を学び始める
How to make these nanotechnology
このナノテクノロジーの作り方
That's because I came back later
後から戻ってきたから
This year is the tenth year in Taiwan
今年は台湾10年目です
Our time is more than nine years
私たちの時間は9年以上です
What I have done in the tenth year is related to this context.
私が10年目に行ったことは、この文脈に関連しています。
So I'll just go straight to what we're doing in this space
それでは、この分野で私たちが何をしているのかに直接行きます
good
良い
Before we start talking about regeneration
再生について話し始める前に
I would like to introduce a very interesting research
とても興味深い研究を紹介したいと思います
I like to share with you
あなたと共有するのが好きです
This is a cross-border cooperation between the United States and Egypt
これは米国とエジプトの間の国境を越えた協力です
what to do
何をすべきか
Here is the mummy of an Egyptian 3,000 years ago
これは3000年前のエジプト人のミイラです
It's a princess mummy
プリンセスミイラです
get the mummy out
ミイラを連れ出す
Whole-body computed tomography scan
全身コンピュータ断層撮影スキャン
that can be seen very white
とても白く見える
brighter ones
明るいもの
It's where the arteriosclerosis is
動脈硬化が起こっているところです
The one on the right is a modern Egyptian
この右側は現代のエジプト人です
It's the same as doing a full-body computerized tomography examination.
全身のコンピューター断層撮影検査を行うのと同じです。
same white as this
これと同じ白
They all represent places where arteriosclerosis is covered
それらはすべて動脈硬化が起こっている場所を表しています
You can see that
それがわかります
From the aorta of our heart, the spectator artery, to
私たちの心臓の大動脈である観客の動脈から、
From the aorta in our abdomen to the two feet these branches
腹部の大動脈から両足まで、これらの枝は
In fact, the gap of three thousand years
実は三千年の隔たり
did not cause much change in the disease of arteriosclerosis
動脈硬化の病気には大きな変化を引き起こさなかった
That is to say, even after three thousand years of evolution
つまり、3000年の進化を経ても
The disease is still
病気はまだある
i joked
冗談を言いました
If our air continues to deteriorate like it has these days
このまま空気が悪化し続けたら
Can human beings live on the earth for another 3,000 years?
人類はあと3000年も地球上で生きられるでしょうか？
may be a problem
問題があるかもしれない
but if you can
でもできれば
After 3000 years, we will take people out to make
3000年後、私たちは人々を連れ出して何かを作ります
Whole body computerized tomography scan
全身コンピューター断層撮影スキャン
maybe still like this
たぶんまだこんな感じ
In other words, arteriosclerosis is actually an ancient disease.
つまり、動脈硬化は実は古くからある病気なのです。
It's not like this today because everyone eats well
みんなよく食べるから今日はこんなんじゃないよ
OK
OK
So what's the problem with hardening?
では、硬化すると何が問題になるのでしょうか？
If this blood vessel hardens, it will become narrower and narrower
この血管が硬くなるとどんどん細くなっていきます
The blood cannot run through, or even be blocked.
血液が流れることはなく、遮断されることさえありません。
If we block our brains, we will have a stroke
脳をブロックすると脳卒中を起こします
Myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞
If the feet are blocked, the feet will turn black
足がふさがると足が黒くなる
If the intestines are blocked, the intestines will turn black
腸が詰まると腸が黒くなります
OK
OK
What happens in the heart is what we call a myocardial infarction
心臓で起こることが心筋梗塞と呼ばれるものです
Then I often remind my friends
それから私はよく友達に思い出させます
In Taiwan we are all cultural cancer
台湾では私たちは皆文化の癌です
We all know that cancer is the number one cause of death in Taiwan
台湾の死因の第1位がガンであることは誰もが知っています。
we all know that
我々はすべてそれを知っている
But that's all cancers added up
しかし、それはすべての癌を合計したものです
If we look at individual organs
個々の臓器を見てみると
The heart is still the single organ that kills the most people in the country
心臓は依然としてこの国で最も多くの人の命を奪う臓器である
Please keep this in mind for a chance to encourage heart research like this
このような心臓研究を促進する機会として、このことを念頭に置いてください。
Then if it is because of the main color of the arteries
それが動脈の主な色によるものである場合
cause myocardial necrosis
心筋壊死を引き起こす
Our heart itself doesn't regenerate very well
私たちの心自体はなかなか再生しません
Everyone may know this
これは誰でも知っているかもしれません
Necrotic myocardium will slowly fibrosis
壊死した心筋はゆっくりと線維化する
It will be like the gray and white place here
ここは灰色と白の場所のようになるでしょう
This red one is our special dyeing
この赤いのは弊社の特別な染色です
叫Tricon Staining
×トリコン染色
live cardiac tissue
生きた心臓組織
still dyed red
まだ赤く染まっている
fibrotic, hardened
線維化した、硬化した
The myocardium without function will turn grayish white
機能を失った心筋は灰白色になります
You can see that I used another cartoon instead
代わりに別の漫画を使用していることがわかります
That is to say, the position of myocardial necrosis
つまり、心筋壊死の位置
it gradually becomes thinner
徐々に薄くなっていきます
become thinner
薄くなる
But our hearts keep saying
でも私たちの心は言い続ける
The heart is the hardest working organ in our body
心臓は私たちの体の中で最も働きやすい臓器です
From when you were inside your mother's womb
お母さんのお腹の中にいる時から
it starts jumping
飛び跳ね始める
ten weeks it started jumping
10週間で飛び始めた
skip till you are born skip till you grow up
生まれるまでスキップ 大人になるまでスキップ
Jump to you one day getting old enough to go away
いつかあなたにジャンプして、去っていくのに十分な年齢になる
it keeps jumping
それは飛び続けます
jumping all the time
ずっとジャンプしてる
can't stop
止まらない
In the process of shrinking and jumping
縮んで飛び跳ねる過程で
it will get thinner for this
これで薄くなるよ
Compare
比較
Relatively less powerful
比較的威力が低い
That mind-blowing pair creates pressure
その驚異的なペアがプレッシャーを生み出す
so it pushes it
それでそれを押します
let it bash out
それを叩きのめしましょう
If you slam it, it will pull the more normal scheming
叩きつければもっと普通の陰謀が起こるだろう
cause secondary damage
二次被害を引き起こす
So this heart will slowly grow bigger and bigger
だからこの心はゆっくり大きくなっていきます
getting bigger and bigger
どんどん大きくなる
become not only bigger but also thinner
大きくなるだけでなく薄くなります
So the heart can contract like this
だから心臓はこうやって収縮できるんだ
That's because of partial heart attack
それは部分的な心臓発作のせいです
one day it will be like this
いつかこうなるだろう
Shrinkage agent is weak
収縮剤が弱い
Books and chapters have no strength
本や章には強度がない
So this is actually true of one of our patient's chest s-lights
これは、実際に私たちの患者の胸部 S ライトの 1 つに当てはまります。
Everyone has had chest s-rays
各位都照過胸部S光
The shaded part of white is the patient's heart
白い影の部分が患者の心臓です
If you have any impression, remember
印象に残っていることがあれば覚えておいてください
Go back and compare the S light you made
自分が作ったSライトを遡って比較してみよう
You know your heart is probably like this
君の心はきっとこんな感じだよ
For this patient, we usually calculate the ratio of chest enlargement and heart reduction
この患者の場合、通常、胸部の拡大と心臓の縮小の比率を計算します。
This patient has probably reached 85% to almost 90%
この患者はおそらく 85% からほぼ 90% に達しています
We normal people are usually only about 50%
私たち普通の人は通常約50％しかありません
So when a heart is so dirty
だから心がとても汚れているときは
he can only be like this
彼はこうするしかない
So you can imagine if this patient can go for a jog
この患者がジョギングに行けるかどうか想像できます
is there a way to go up and down the stairs
階段を上り下りする方法はありますか
There's not even a way he can just lie on the bed and ship
彼がただベッドに横たわって船に乗る方法さえありません
even if he started with a localized heart problem
たとえ彼が局所的な心臓の問題から始まったとしても
How can we help such a patient?
どうすればそのような患者を助けることができるでしょうか？
Do you want to guess what there is a thing over here?
ここに何があるのか​​当ててみませんか?
This is called a war machine
これを戦争機械と呼ぶ
difibrator
ディフィブレーター
Because this patient is normally like this
この患者さんは普段からこんな感じなので
he's become like this now
彼は今こうなりました
sometimes he's like this
時々彼はこうなります
what to do at this time
このとき何をすべきか
Hurry up pad
急いでパッド
or to press
または押す
to do CPR
心肺蘇生をする
Otherwise the patient will rest immediately
そうしないと、患者はすぐに休んでしまいます
please remember
思い出してください
If you encounter such a situation around you
もしあなたの周りでそのような状況に遭遇したら
someone exposed
誰かが暴露した
you feel his pulse in the neck
あなたは彼の首の脈動を感じます
don't touch your hands touch your neck
手に触れないでください首に触れてください
The neck is the most clearly palpable
首が一番はっきりとわかります
if you can't feel your pulse
脈拍を感じられない場合
don't do anything
何もしないでください
Don't go to the Human Services Association, don't rush him
福祉協会には行かないでください、彼を急かさないでください
direct pressure
直圧
it's ok
それでおしまい
but first thing
でもまず第一に
What is CPR first thing
まず心肺蘇生とは何ですか
right
右
Call help
助けを呼ぶ
hurry up
急げ
Hurry up and call 119
急いで119番に電話してください
call for help
助けを呼びます
Not mouth to mouth or pressure
口移しや圧力ではありません
neither
ない
The first thing in CPR is called call help
心肺蘇生法で最初に行うことは、ヘルプコールと呼ばれます
find someone to help
助けてくれる人を見つける
then press
次に、 を押します
The latest concept
最新のコンセプト
you don't need artificial respiration
人工呼吸は必要ありません
Just keep pressing, pressing, pressing
ただ押し続けて押し続けてください
Just push until someone comes to help.
誰かが助けに来るまで押し続けてください。
don't mess with electricity
電気をいじらないでください
If you can feel his pulse
彼の脈拍を感じられたら
you don't need electricity
電気は必要ありません
Because he was still dancing normally
まだ普通に踊ってたから
He might be finished after being shocked by you.
彼はあなたにショックを受けて終わってしまうかもしれません。
so don't mess with electricity
だから電気をいじらないでください
I will remind you every time
毎回思い出させます
Because our children's elementary school used to be
なぜなら、私たちの子供たちの小学校はかつて
The principal of the primary school asked me
小学校の校長先生が私に尋ねました。
Everything needs to be placed where the electrical appliances should be placed.
電化製品を置くべき場所にすべてを置く必要があります。
sometimes it's better not to let go
時には手放さない方が良いこともある
It's actually dangerous
実は危険なんです
Such patients we
そのような患者様を私たちは
Usually that's the way to help him
通常、それが彼を助ける方法です
heart transplant
心臓移植
But we don't have that many hearts to transplant
でも移植する心臓はそんなに多くない
especially in taiwan
特に台湾では
so
それで
Even today, there are one hundred patients waiting for patients with heart disease at National Taiwan University Hospital every day.
今でも国立台湾大学病院では毎日100人の患者が心臓病の患者を待っている。
come help
助けに来てください
Every day, 150 people in Taiwan are waiting for heart surgery to save their lives
台湾では毎日150人が命を救うために心臓手術を待っている
We don't have that many hearts to suffer from
私たちには苦しむ心はそれほど多くない
But these patients are still poor
しかし、これらの患者は依然として貧しい
Don't you think he has only one patient and he's affecting the whole family
彼の患者は一人だけなのに、家族全員に影響を与えているとは思いませんか
When there are a hundred families with this patient saying he affects a community or even a
この患者の家族が100人もいて、彼が地域社会、さらには社会に影響を及ぼしていると言っているとしたら、
nation
国家
it's actually serious
それは実際には深刻です
So what we want to be able to do is is there a way
それで、私たちができるようにしたいのは、方法はあるのかということです
we can
我々はできる
I just said
私はちょうど言いました
After 3,000 years, people may still have sexual arousal
3000年後も人々は性的興奮を持っている可能性がある
we knew he would be like this
彼がこうなるだろうと私たちは知っていた
But we hope he doesn't change like this
でも彼がこのように変わらないことを願っています
or at least not like this
または少なくともこれはそうではありません
No patient like this will come in for a new operation
こんな患者は新たな手術を受けに来ないだろう
How to do it
どうやってするの
There may be several ways
いくつかの方法があるかもしれません
First
初め
Let's protect the heart muscle early
早めに心筋を守りましょう
because
なぜなら
After the blood vessel is blocked
血管が詰まった後
Myocardial hypoxia-ischemia
心筋低酸素虚血
Myocardial necrosis may occur immediately
すぐに心筋壊死が起こる可能性がある
Taiwan's medical system is actually very good.
実は台湾の医療制度はとても充実しています。
Don't worry about whether the country's finances can afford it
国の財政に余裕があるかどうかを心配する必要はありません
It's really one of our biggest
それは本当に私たちの最大の一つです
one
一個
The people's welfare, I'm honest
国民の福祉、正直に言うと
Of course some people have to be sacrificed
もちろん犠牲にならなければいけない人もいる
Only by sacrificing some talents can we say that Taiwan's medical quality is good, convenient and cheap
一部の人材を犠牲にして初めて、台湾の医療の質が良く、便利で、安いと言えるのです
People must be sacrificed, otherwise there is no such good thing in the world
人は犠牲にならなければならない、そうでなければこの世にこんな良いものはない
Sacrificial groups include
犠牲グループには以下が含まれます：
Standing in front of this one like this
こうやってこの人の前に立って
ignore him
彼を無視する
now in taiwan
今台湾にいます
All we can do is patients with myocardial infarction
私たちにできることは心筋梗塞患者さんだけです
sent to emergency room
救急治療室に送られる
after
後
He was diagnosed with a myocardial infarction, and his blood vessels must be opened within 90 minutes.
彼は心筋梗塞と診断され、90分以内にできるだけ早く血管を広げる必要がある。
you can hit
あなたは打つことができます
Thrombotropic Drugs
血栓形成薬
You can also go straight to a new catheter
新しいカテーテルに直接進むこともできます
You can put the bracket
スタンドも置けます
but within 90 minutes
ただし90分以内
It is necessary to complete this operation
この操作を完了する必要があります
this process
このプロセス
Why? Because after a myocardial infarction
なぜかというと、心筋梗塞の後だからです。
Only 4 hours to 6 hours
たったの4時間から6時間
It can be used to protect the heart muscle
心筋を保護するために使用できます
beyond this time
この時間を超えて
What I'm doing may be superfluous
私のやっていることは余計なことかもしれない
it doesn't help much
あまり役に立ちません
So this is to protect the heart muscle early
これは心筋を早期に保護するためです
OK
OK
the second one
2番目のもの
if we...
もし私達...
because it is an ischemic
虚血だから
hypoxia problem
低酸素の問題
blood vessel problem
血管の問題
So if we can do therapeutic
それで、もし私たちが治療を行うことができれば、
increase its blood vessels
血管を増やす
grow more blood vessels
より多くの血管を成長させる
Of course it will help the function of the heart
もちろん心臓の働きも良くなります
The third
第3
you know its dead part
あなたはその死んだ部分を知っています
will eventually become thinner and thinner
最終的にはどんどん薄くなっていきます
If you can punch it in and inject some material
パンチインして材料を注入できれば
some business material
何らかのビジネス資料
or drugs
または麻薬
can make this mind coin
この心をコインにできる
Even if it is necrotic it will not thin
壊死しても薄くならない
Then it can maintain its strength
そうすれば強度を維持できる
so the heart can sustain it to continue the surgery
心臓が手術を継続できるように維持するため
won't be beaten
負けないよ
then if it has thinned
それで薄くなっていたら
but not too big
でも大きすぎない
then we can do...
それなら私たちはできる...
is to make a whole heart muscle
心筋全体を作ることです
It's like we're mending clothes
まるで服を繕っているみたいだ
patch it to the outside of the heart
心臓の外側にパッチを当てます
Let it contract with the heart
心で収縮させてください
You guys think I'm talking about cartoons
君たちは私が漫画のことを話していると思っているだろうか
Taiwanese called official card
台湾のオフィシャルカードと呼ばれる
In fact, all these are being done
実際、これらはすべて行われています
We are all doing it
みんなでやってるよ
Many people all over the world are doing
世界中で多くの人がやっている
I will take some examples today
今日はいくつか例を挙げて説明します
Everyone for reference
皆様、ご参考までに
The other one is actually our favorite
もう一つは実際に私たちのお気に入りです
This is our unique trick
これが私たちのユニークなトリックです
Although we were the first to do
私たちが最初にやったのに
prove this thing
このことを証明してください
That is to say, it is supplementing the five types of animals
つまり5種類の動物を補っているのです
Including mice, including humans, of course
もちろんマウスも含めて人間も含めて
In fact, after our heart muscle is damaged
実際、心筋が損傷すると、
It triggers in our body
それは私たちの体の中で引き起こされます
endogenous stem cells
内因性幹細胞
it goes to where this damaged heart muscle
それはこの損傷した心筋の場所に行きます
to regenerate
再生する
it grows some cardiomyocytes
いくつかの心筋細胞を成長させます
but few
しかし少ない
So however we are the first to prove that
しかし、私たちはそれを最初に証明しました
really have this thing
本当にこれを持っています
Of course there's one thing that's going to happen on Earth
もちろん、地球上で起こることが一つあります
just not enough
ただ十分ではない
then once you understand it
それを理解したら
you can find ways to stimulate
刺激する方法を見つけることができます
make it more
もっと作る
if this never happened
もしこれが起こらなかったら
you have to make something out of nothing
何もないところから何かを生み出さなければならない
probably more difficult
おそらくもっと難しい
So all we have to do is
それで私たちがしなければならないのは、
how to find this
これを見つける方法
Where are the endogenous stem cells?
内因性幹細胞はどこにあるのでしょうか?
how it is activated
どのように活性化されるのか
is there a way to take a medicine
薬を飲む方法はありますか
can make this regenerative ability stronger
この再生能力をより強力にすることができます
Ours is actually our favorite
私たちのものは実際に私たちのお気に入りです
its spontaneous endogeneity
その自発的な内生性
original ability to regenerate
本来の再生能力
Okay, then I will mainly introduce to you today.
それでは、今日は主に紹介させていただきます。
three things
三個東西
The first is our endogenous stem cells
1つ目は内因性幹細胞です
how to regenerate heart muscle
心筋を再生する方法
The second one is to tell you
2つ目はあなたに伝えることです
How can we use tissue engineering
組織工学をどのように活用できるか
Combining biomedicine and engineering
生物医学と工学の融合
Three ways to help the heart repair and regenerate
心臓の修復と再生を助ける 3 つの方法
the third one
3番目の
recent news
最近のニュース
The news is a little louder
ニュースが少し大きくなりました
How do we use wearing stem cells
身に着けている幹細胞をどのように使用するか
or induced pluripotent stem cells
または人工多能性幹細胞
These early stem cells come from
これらの初期幹細胞は、
cardiomyocytes
心筋細胞
and then let it become mature cardiomyocytes
そしてそれを成熟した心筋細胞にさせます
We can use it for drug picking
麻薬ピッキングに使えます
able to be used for treatment
治療に使用できる
I'll start with the endogenous relationship package
内生的関係パッケージから始めます
everyone look at this
みんなこれを見て
I think most people may not understand
多分ほとんどの人は理解できないと思う
Even explaining to the professor three times in medicine
医学では教授に3回も説明するのに
He doesn't necessarily know how to listen and tell the truth
彼は真実の聞き方や伝え方を必ずしも知っているわけではない
so i just jump over
だから私はただ飛び越えます
But I tell you, please believe me
でも、言っておきますが、信じてください
Now that you're here, you just have to trust me
ここにいるからには、あとは私を信頼するだけです
We really have a group of endogenous relationship packages in us
私たちの中には実際に内生的な関係パッケージのグループが存在します
Can go to regenerate scheming
計画を再生成することができます
what did we do
私たちは何をしましたか
we found that
私たちはそれを見つけました
This is of course a mouse
これはもちろんマウスです
We all love using mice for animal models
私たちは皆、動物モデルにマウスを使うのが大好きです
Not because mice are easy to bully
ネズミがいじめやすいからではない
It means that the mouse is one of the five types of animals
ネズミは5種類の動物のうちの1つであることを意味します
Then we make transgenic mice
次にトランスジェニックマウスを作ります
A lot of people around the world do it and we do it too
世界中の多くの人がそうしており、私たちもそうしています
So the transgenic mouse
そこでトランスジェニックマウス
Transgenic mice are easier to make
トランスジェニックマウスの作製が容易になる
So let's take it and make our animal model
それを使って動物モデルを作りましょう
If in mice we can see good results
マウスで良い結果が得られれば
then we'll jump up
それから私たちは飛び上がります
Larger animals even become humans
大きな動物も人間になる
So the mouse is actually more
つまり、マウスは実際にはもっと多くのものです
that contributed a lot
それは大いに貢献した
Of course I'm talking about rats, experimental animals.
もちろん、私は実験動物であるラットについて話しています。
It's not the rats that come and go in your house.
家に出入りするのはネズミではありません。
not the same
不太一樣
We use a more complex gene rotor mouse model
より複雑な遺伝子ローター マウス モデルを使用します。
first time to prove that
それを証明するのは初めて
After myocardial infarction in mice
マウスの心筋梗塞後
Parts with necrosis and parts without necrosis
壊死のある部分と壊死のない部分
We call this the middle ground
これを中間点と呼びます
It will be a place where the stem cells are most active
幹細胞が最も活発に活動する場所になります。
15% of stem cells grow new heart muscle
幹細胞の 15% が新しい心筋を成長させる
to fix it
それを直すために
Then you will think that 15% is a lot.
そうすれば、15% は多いと思うでしょう。
yeah 15% is a lot
そうですね、15%は多いですね
But it's only around the necrosis
でもそれは壊死の周りだけです
that small circle around
その周りの小さな円
That lap is 15%
そのラップは15%です
Going outside leaves only 5%, 7% or even nothing
外に出ても5%か7%しか残らない、あるいは何も残らない
So it's definitely not enough for the whole heart
だから心全体には絶対に足りない
So we want to say how can we
それで私たちはどうすればよいかを言いたいのです
Find out where these endogenous stem cells come from
これらの内因性幹細胞がどこから来たのかを調べる
then we can stimulate it
そうすればそれを刺激することができます
Let it generate more new muscle regeneration
より多くの新しい筋肉の再生を引き起こします
Then this study started when I was waiting for Boss
そして、ボスを待っているときにこの研究が始まりました
and then later
そしてその後
two PhD students
2人の博士課程の学生
Welcome Zhang and American side Jasmin
チャンとアメリカ側のジャスミンを歓迎します
they all graduated
彼らは全員卒業しました
Jasmin is currently working as a postdoctoral fellow in Germany
ジャスミンは現在ドイツで博士研究員として働いています。
Welcome to Zhang Zai, former president of the State Council
元国務院主席の張載氏へようこそ
Experimenters I can know as postdoctoral fellows
ポスドクとして知り合える実験者
They did the first study
彼らは最初の研究を行いました
Just do this study
この勉強だけをしてください
that is
あれは
After myocardial infarction in mice
マウスの心筋梗塞後
How does he have an endogenous dry bag to regenerate heart muscle
彼はどのようにして心筋を再生するための内因性ドライバッグを持っているのでしょうか？
how long does he need
彼はどれくらい時間が必要ですか
what time is the most important
一番大切な時間は何時ですか
So we did a very simple experiment
そこで私たちは非常に簡単な実験を行いました
After myocardial infarction in mice
マウスの心筋梗塞後
Seven days Ten days Fourteen days Twenty-one days Twenty-eight days
7日間 10日間 14日間 21日間 28日間
Fifty-six days to eighty-four days to three months
56日から84日から3ヶ月
Let's talk about this dry bag
このドライバッグについて話しましょう
How to regenerate heart muscle
心筋を再生する方法
Our original thought was
私たちの当初の考えは
a little every day a little every day
毎日少しずつ 毎日少しずつ
15% in the end
最後有15%
Surprisingly, it was found
驚いたことに、見つかったのです
Actually not like this
実際はそうではありません
seven days
七日間
There is a clear dry package that regenerates the myocardium
心筋を再生する透明なドライパッケージがあります
It's over in ten days
あと10日で終わります
you've been waiting for no more
あなたはもう待っていません
Dry pack regenerates heart muscle
ドライパックで心筋を再生
This is actually an interesting result
これは実に興味深い結果です
What do you guys think of a picture like this
このような写真を見て皆さんはどう思いますか
That's seven days and ten days
それは7日と10日です
But do you know how much time we spent on this picture
でも、この写真にどれだけの時間を費やしたか知っていますか？
Eighteen million five years to get this result
この結果が得られるまでに 1,800 万 5 年かかります
I won't talk about the details anymore.
それについては詳しくは説明しません
Then we found out that since it will be so soon
それから私たちはそれがもうすぐなので、
Stem cells are primed after cell suffocation
幹細胞は細胞窒息後にプライミングされる
So what is the signal and what mechanism to stimulate it?
それでは、信号とは何であり、それを刺激するメカニズムは何でしょうか?
you will want to say
と言いたくなるでしょう
What happened to Xinji infarction
新吉梗塞はどうなったのか
What happened when your hand was cut with a knife?
手をナイフで切ったときはどうなりましたか？
What happens if your hand is cut with a knife?
手をナイフで切ったらどうなりますか？
It hurts, of course it hurts
痛いです、もちろん痛いです
redness hot pain
紅 腫 熱 痛
The inflammatory reaction we are talking about is redness, swelling, heat, pain
私たちが話している炎症反応とは、赤み、腫れ、熱、痛みです。
red why red
赤、なぜ赤
Of course the first blood will be red
もちろん最初の血は赤いだろう
But if you have tissues in your body, you will dirty a lot of capillaries
しかし、体内に組織があると、多くの毛細血管が汚れてしまいます。
so it will be red
だから赤くなるよ
why is it swollen
なぜ腫れているのですか
Because the blood vessel ruptures, the tissue will come out
血管が破れるので組織が飛び出す
If blood comes out, it will swell
血が出れば腫れる
it's hot why is it hot
暑いですなぜ暑いのですか
because its partial like
部分的に似ているので
It can only be repaired, so it will be hot
修理しかできないので暑いです
Why does it hurt?
なぜ痛いのですか？
because of the pressure on the nerve
神経が圧迫されるため
or you release a lot of tissue
または大量の組織を放出します
it stimulates your peripheral nerves
末梢神経を刺激します
so you will hurt
だからあなたは傷つくでしょう
OK as long as the body is injured
体に傷があればOK
You will be red, hot, painful and inflamed
赤く、熱く、痛み、炎症を起こすでしょう
Myocardial infarction too
心筋梗塞も
So when we take medicine
だから私たちが薬を飲むときは
to suppress your inflammatory response
炎症反応を抑えるために
You won't be in pain, you won't be red, swollen and hot
痛みもないし、赤くなったり、腫れたり、熱くなったりすることもない
But you also suppress your relationship package
しかし、あなたは自分の関係パッケージも抑制します
It just won't come out, there's no heart muscle regeneration
出てこないだけで、心筋の再生はありません
OK
OK
OK, so if we use
OK、それでは、
you suppress the inflammatory response
炎症反応を抑制します
Relationship package won't come out
関係パッケージが出てこない
then if i stimulate it
それで刺激したら
make it more inflammatory
さらに炎症を起こさせる
Will more related packages come out?
関連パッケージはさらに登場するでしょうか?
Really, but you have to stimulate the right
本当に、でも正しい刺激をしなければなりません
you need to give the right medicine
適切な薬を与える必要があります
Giving the wrong medicine won't help
間違った薬を与えても効果はありません
Then we found that there is a prostaglandin E2
すると、プロスタグランジンE2という物質があることが分かりました。
called PGE2
PGE2と呼ばれる
It can stimulate more stem packs
より多くのステムパッケージを刺激することができます
can become cardiomyocytes
心筋細胞になることができる
From 15% to 20%
15%から20%へ
then next
それから次へ
The problem is that we usually do mice
問題は、私たちが普段マウスを使っていることです。
It's all done with young mice
すべては若いネズミで行われます
Because it's cheaper, faster, and simpler
そのほうが安くて早くて簡単だから
But we know patients who say they will have a myocardial infarction
しかし、私たちは心筋梗塞になるだろうと言う患者を知っています。
In fact, they are relatively older
実際、彼らは比較的年上です
Although I also recently heard
私も最近聞いたのですが、
An 18-year-old had a myocardial infarction
18歳の少年が心筋梗塞を起こした
It is true that age has declined
年齢が下がったのは事実
but generally speaking
しかし一般的に言えば
Most common myocardial infarction patients are older
最も一般的な心筋梗塞患者は高齢者です
Of course we have to use older ones for mice
もちろん、マウスには古いものを使用する必要があります
Surprisingly, we found that
驚いたことに、私たちは次のことを発見しました。
older mice
古いマウス
It's normal after a myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞後は正常です
Its stem cells will not regenerate heart muscle
その幹細胞は心筋を再生しません
But if you put our PGE2
しかし、私たちのPGE2を入れたら
The limit of this potential can be punched in
この可能性の限界を打ち破ることができる
It can restore the same ability as when it was young
幼い頃と同じ能力を取り戻すことができる
15% of myocardium's ability to regenerate
心筋の再生能力の15%
This experiment is actually very important
この実験は実はとても重要です
British all over the world
世界中のイギリス人
The President of the New University Association came to Taiwan to give a speech
新大学協会会長が講演のため台湾に来ました
He also helped us publicize that this great strength is really important.
彼はまた、この大きな強みが本当に重要であることを宣伝するのにも協力してくれました。
why is it important
どうしてそれが重要ですか
because he told us
彼が私たちに言ったから
You worry that when people are getting older and older
人々がどんどん年をとっていくとき、あなたは心配します。
Are the stem cells gone?
幹細胞がなくなってしまったのでしょうか？
Or stem cells don't work
それとも幹細胞が機能しないのか
It looks like this
こんな感じです
But after stimulating us with drugs
しかし、薬物で私たちを刺激した後、
In fact, stem cells still work
実は幹細胞は今も働いている
This represents two meanings
これは2つの意味を表しています
The first one even though older
古いものでも最初のもの
Stem cells are still there
幹細胞はまだ残っている
there is still hope
まだ希望はある
It's not that when you get older
歳を取るとそうでもないよ
it's still there
それはまだそこにあります
But it may be affected by some volitional factor
しかし、それは何らかの意志的な要因によって影響される可能性があります
hold it down
それを押してください
Make these stem cells useless
これらの幹細胞を役に立たなくする
So if you can unravel the mystery
それで謎が解けたら
Allow stem cells to regain their ability
幹細胞がその能力を取り戻すことができるようにする
Then we can regenerate the new machine
その後、新しいマシンを再生成できます
PG-2 is one of those that can do such a job
PG-2 はそのような仕事ができるものの 1 つです
PG-2 is a drug that mainly removes
PG-2は主に除去する薬です。
factor of our aging
私たちの老化の要因
One of them is called TGF-Fatalone
そのうちの1つはTGF-ファタロンと呼ばれます
Pressure-free is not very familiar with these
プレッシャーフリーはこれらについてあまり馴染みがありません
it doesn't matter you know
あなたが知っていても問題ありません
Anyway, there are many genes
とにかく遺伝子が多い
this is one of the genes
これは遺伝子の一つです
So PG-2 Treatment can
したがって、PG-2 治療は次のことが可能です。
Beta this Cinema of TG in the aging heart
老いた心にあるTGのシネマをベータ版で
hold it down
それを押してください
So the lid cell can regain its ability to regenerate
そのため、まぶたの細胞は再生能力を取り戻すことができます。
So if we directly give
したがって、直接与えると
This drug that inhibits the beta of TG
TGのβを阻害する薬です
we can restore some degree of
ある程度は復元できます
Scheming regenerated in the old you mouse
古いマウスで再生された陰謀
So, if there are friends from the pharmacy here,
それで、ここに薬局の友達がいたら、
you will know
あなたは知るだろう
There are at least two things that can be developed
開発できることが少なくとも 2 つあります
Drugs for Cardiac Regeneration
心臓再生薬
One is called Pg2
1つはPg2と呼ばれます
One called TGβ1
TGβ1と呼ばれるもの
Right, that is it
そう、それです
The next question is
次の質問は
Where did these stem cells come from?
これらの幹細胞はどこから来たのでしょうか?
Most of the stem cells are actually in the heart
幹細胞のほとんどは実際には心臓にあります
from the heart
心の底から
It wouldn't move
動かないだろう
then you stimulate it
それからあなたはそれを刺激します
it will start to work
それは機能し始めるでしょう
But there is one thing everyone agrees on
しかし、誰もが同意することが1つあります
But there is one thing that everyone has been controversial about.
しかし、誰もが物議を醸していることが1つあります。
Tonic in the bone marrow
骨髄の強壮剤
or blood circulation
または血液循環
Are there any stem cells that can regenerate the brain?
脳を再生できる幹細胞はあるのでしょうか？
we are very clear that
私たちはそれを非常に明確にしています
after myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞後
It's the same with people
それは人も同じです
you are going to mend
あなたは直すつもりです
repair your heart muscle
心筋を修復する
You will be in the blood circulation from the bone marrow
骨髄からの血液循環になります
There will be a lot of stem cells will come out
幹細胞がたくさん出てきます
Run to the heart to grow new blood vessels
新しい血管を成長させるために心臓に向かって走る
turn into new cells to repair
新しい細胞に変わって修復する
we already know this
私たちはすでにこれを知っています
But these bone marrow or blood circulation cells
しかし、これらの骨髄細胞や血液循環細胞は
Can it become new cardiomyocytes?
新しい心筋細胞になれるでしょうか？
everyone speaks differently
誰もが違う話し方をする
so we engage our gene transfer agency
そこで私たちは遺伝子導入機関と協力します
And let's bully the mice again
そしてまたネズミをいじめましょう
Seal two mice together
2匹のマウスを一緒に封印する
so that his blood can be exchanged
彼の血が交換できるように
so we can study his genes
そうすれば彼の遺伝子を研究できる
so our first
それで私たちの最初の
It is also the first time to prove that
それを証明したのも初めてだ
In fact, the blood circulation
実は血液循環は
There is still a population of stem cells after myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞後も幹細胞の集団が存在する
Not only does he go to the heart to help with repairs
彼は修理を手伝うために全力を尽くすだけではありません
He will even turn directly into cardiomyocytes
彼は心筋細胞に直接変化することさえある
This is an important contribution of our study
これは私たちの研究の重要な貢献です
good
良い
Another study is
別の研究は、
is there any other way
他に方法はありますか
In addition to drug stimulation
薬物刺激に加えて
If I grow more blood vessels
もっと血管が増えたら
Would it also help endogenous myocardial regeneration
内因性心筋再生にも役立つでしょうか
When all your fields are barren
すべての畑が不毛のとき
it's hard for you to grow
あなたが成長するのは難しいです
grow crops
作物を育てる
But if you open several channels
しかし、複数のチャネルを開いている場合は、
can irrigate
灌漑できる
after water can go in
水が入る可能性がある後
you may grow new crops
新しい作物を育てるかもしれない
Xinzang is also like this
新蔵もこんな感じ
So in another study
そこで別の研究では
This is my other one
これは私のもう一つです
this is my first PhD student
これは私の最初の博士課程の学生です
Later, he also stayed in the laboratory as a postdoctoral fellow.
その後、博士研究員として研究室に留まりました。
Now working as a postdoctoral fellow at Harvard
現在はハーバード大学で博士研究員として働いています
Previous year at MIT
前年のMIT
In the next year at Harvard like this
翌年ハーバードではこうして
It is the first student in my lab
それは私の研究室の最初の学生です
everyone jokes
みんなが冗談を言う
Usually there is a
通常、
The first student call is always the best
学生の最初の電話は常に最高です
it's that kind
それはその種類です
Anyway, everyone can't get the award
とにかく全員が賞を取れるわけではない
the whole world for example
たとえば全世界
young student scientist
若い学生科学者
There are 10 bonuses that can be obtained
獲得できるボーナスは10個
The only one in Asia is him
アジアには彼だけだ
Has won this award three times
この賞を3回受賞しています
very good student
とても良い学生
One of the studies is
研究の一つは、
we found that
私たちはそれを見つけました
If we use another rice-resistant glue
他の耐米糊を使う場合
combined with a growth factor
成長因子と組み合わせると
When more blood vessels can grow
より多くの血管が成長できるとき
Whether it is in Dashu or in pigs
大州であろうと豚であろうと
We can all grow more blood vessels
私たちは皆、より多くの血管を成長させることができます
and arterial blood vessels
そして動脈血管
Not capillaries, but arterial blood vessels
毛細血管ではなく動脈血管です
arteries like this
このような動脈
can even help inside our rotorrat
ローターラットの内部でも役立ちます
to prove that it can grow new cardiac tissue
新しい心臓組織を成長させることができることを証明するため
These new cardiac tissues
これらの新しい心臓組織は
It was born from the relationship report
交際報告から生まれました
I finished the first part
最初の部分を終えました
In the second part, I will go further to introduce this
後編ではさらに詳しく紹介していきます
How do we do tissue engineered myocardial regeneration
組織工学による心筋再生はどのように行うのか
This is actually my postdoc boss.
実はこれが私のポスドクの上司です。
One that Yu Qiuli and the others sorted out before
Yu Qiuliたちが以前に解決したもの
for heart cell therapy
心臓細胞治療用
What difficulties and problems will you encounter?
どのような困難や問題に遭遇するでしょうか?
You need to report treatment
治療報告が必要です
Of course you have to have a relationship report first
もちろん最初に交際報告をしなければなりません
Where did this relationship report come from?
この関係報道はどこから来たのでしょうか?
Is it to be derived from the relationship between embryos in the early stage?
それは初期段階の胚間の関係から導き出されるのだろうか？
Still have to extract it from the body
まだ体から取り出さなければなりません
which one is better
どちらがいいですか
this is a big problem
これは大きな問題です
The second question is
2番目の質問は、
Okay, I already have a relationship report today.
さて、今日はすでに交際報告があります。
become cardiomyocytes
心筋細胞になる
Then how do I report this relationship?
では、この関係をどのように報告すればよいでしょうか?
sent to the heart
心に送られました
where i am going to be treated
どこで治療を受けますか
If you remember, I said at the beginning
覚えていると思いますが、最初に言いました
Although the heart will become so big in the end
心は最後には大きくなるけど
to have a heart transplant
心臓移植を受けるために
But when he first
しかし、彼が最初に
It's just a local problem
それは単なるローカルな問題です
Not the whole heart has to regenerate
心臓全体が再生する必要はない
So when you're doing cell therapy
したがって、細胞療法を行うときは
how do you get these cells
どうやってこれらの細胞を入手するのですか
sent to where you want to regenerate
再生したい場所へ
Very important
とても重要
Today if we want to rely on the head
今日は頭に頼りたいなら
But all your medicine ran out
でも薬がなくなってしまった
or you have to lean on your feet
さもなければ足に寄りかかる必要があります
your medicine ran out
あなたの薬がなくなりました
of course it's useless
もちろん無駄です
This is actually a very important
これは実はとても重要なことなのですが、
a concept
一個concept
you may also
あなたもできます
sometimes want to say
時々言いたいことがある
Why did the doctor tell me to take food today?
なぜ医者は私に今日は食事をするように言ったのですか?
Called me to call yesterday
昨日電話してきました
even told me to suck
吸うようにさえ言った
stick to the skin
肌にくっつく
Various
様々
way to enter the body
体内への入り方
In fact, he is not the same
実際、彼は同じではありません
the same reason
同じ理由
If we want stem cells
幹細胞が欲しいなら
put it in the heart
心の中に入れて
you have to think
考えなければなりません
How can I get stem cells
幹細胞はどうやって入手できますか
can stay
滞在できる
Can be injected where I am going for treatment
治療に行く場所に注射できる
do not forget
忘れてはいけない
the heart keeps contracting
心臓は収縮し続ける
So you hit stem cells into your heart today
だから今日は幹細胞を心臓に打ち込むんだ
no matter through point of view
視点を通してでも構いません
or hit the muscles directly
または筋肉を直接叩く
24 hours later
24時間後
Only 1% of the cells remain in the heart
心臓に残る細胞はわずか1%
others ran away
他の人は逃げた
Even if the 1% of the cells left in the heart
たとえ心臓に細胞が1%残っていたとしても
in 24 hours
24時間以内に
Anyway, all 99 are dead
とにかく99人全員死んだ
Only 1% are still alive
まだ1%しか生き残ってない
say it again
もう一度言ってください
Liver cells go to the heart
肝細胞は心臓へ行く
After a day only 1% is left
一日経つと1%しか残らない
This 1% after another day
さらに一日経つとこの1%
Only 1% are still alive
まだ1%しか生き残ってない
How much does 1% say that 1% is a student
1% が学生であると 1% はどれくらい言いますか
1/10,000
1/10,000
another day
別の日
Gone
消えた
So after 10,000 cells hit the heart
10,000個の細胞が心臓に到達した後
Save one in two days
2日で1個を節約
Another day may not be gone
もう一日が過ぎ去らないかもしれない
This is why we have many clinical trials
だからこそ多くの臨床試験が行われています
Cell Therapy in the Heart
心臓の細胞治療
In fact, there is no way to produce good results
実際には良い結果を生み出す方法はありません
So how can more cells
では、どうすれば細胞を増やすことができるのでしょうか
It's important to keep in the heart
心に留めておくことが大事
and keep it alive
そしてそれを生かし続ける
not only survived
生き残っただけではなく
it turns into cardiomyocytes
それは心筋細胞に変わります
with other cardiomyocytes
他の心筋細胞と
we become good friends
私たちは良い友達になります
can shrink and jump together
縮んで一緒にジャンプすることができます
not it
そうじゃない
ok i stay
わかりました、私はここにいます
I change my mind
気が変わります
heart cells i will say
心臓細胞、私は言います
But I don't care about others
でも他人のことは気にしない
i dance my own
私は自分で踊ります
that's bad
それは良くないね
what is that called
それは何と呼ばれますか
mental disorder
精神障害
worse
悪い
really miserable
本当に惨めな
don't do it
それはしないでください
you did
あなたがやった
After taking stem cells, he was already a patient
幹細胞を投与された後、彼はすでに患者になっていた
As a result, the patient caused him to go to the phone
その結果、患者は彼に電話をかけさせた
going to CPR
心肺蘇生に行く
something will go wrong
何かがうまくいかないだろう
So this is called
それでこれは呼ばれます
electricity
電
Integration of electrical conduction and details
電気伝導と細部の一体化
why is it called
なぜそれが呼ばれるのか
Electro-mechanical integration
電気と機械の統合
Integration of electricity and details
電気と細部の統合
because our cells
なぜなら私たちの細胞は
Between heart cells and cells
心臓の細胞と細胞の間
by ionic conduction
イオン伝導による
electricity like this
こんな電気
boo past
噓過去
Cells know one by one
細胞は一つ一つ知っている
time to work
仕事の時間
It's time to shrink
縮小する時が来た
just shrink together
ただ一緒に縮むだけ
ions turn over
イオンがターンオーバーする
he has the swelling
彼には腫れがある
So it needs to rely on the conduction of electricity
したがって、電気の伝導に依存する必要があります
the heart must contract
心臓は収縮しなければなりません
machine force
機械の力
So this is the integration of the machine world
これが機械世界の統合です
So this is called
それでこれは呼ばれます
Integration of electrical and machine world
電気と機械の世界の統合
叫Electro-mechanical integration
×電気と機械の統合
So the stem cells we injected
そこで私たちが注入した幹細胞は
It needs to be able to become a heart cell
心臓の細胞になれる必要がある
but also with other
しかし、他のものとも
The original cells of the heart integrate together and dance together with hands
心臓の本来の細胞がひとつになって手をつないで踊る
otherwise there will be big problems
そうしないと大きな問題が発生するでしょう
Then this cell therapy only in the heart
では、この細胞療法は心臓だけで
will face the problem
問題に直面するだろう
Cell therapy of organs from other tissues
他の組織からの臓器の細胞治療
will not cause this problem
この問題は発生しません
Then if someone is nervous here, someone will tell me arque
それで誰かがここで緊張していたら、誰かが私にアルクを言うでしょう
Hey, nerves also conduct electricity.
ほら、神経にも電気が通ってるんです。
Then why didn't the nerves take up this problem?
では、なぜ神経はこの問題を取り上げなかったのでしょうか？
then i'll joke
それなら冗談を言います
If your nerve cell therapy
神経細胞療法なら
not doing well it goes wrong
うまくいかない、うまくいかない
At best you ask the patient to raise his right hand
せいぜい患者に右手を上げるように頼むことです
It kicks your left foot with you, it won't die
君と一緒に左足を蹴っても死なないよ
Yes, but if something goes wrong with the cell therapy for the heart
はい、ただし心臓の細胞治療に何か問題が発生した場合は
obviously something goes wrong
明らかに何かが間違っています
would be a big problem
大きな問題になるだろう
So this is still different
だからこれはまだ違う
In the end, of course, we are doing clinical cell therapy
もちろん、最終的には臨床細胞治療を行っています。
is to consider its safety and stability
安全性と安定性を考慮することです
this is very important
これはとても重要です
Let's first talk about how the cells
セルの入れ方について話しましょう
Get to where you are going for treatment
治療を受けに行く場所に行く
Then we use a
次に、
Water glue called Eco-resistant rice fiber
耐環境性米繊維と呼ばれるハイドロゲル
This water gel is from when we were at MIT
このウォータージェルは私たちがMITにいたときのものです
Developed in partnership with MIT
MITとの提携により開発
it's basically a unit of protein
それは基本的にタンパク質の単位です
specially synthesized
所特殊合成的
special sequence of amino acid synthesis
アミノ酸合成の特別な順序
This water can be brought
このお水は持ち込み可能です
We inject directly into the site of myocardial ischemia and hypoxia
心筋虚血・低酸素状態の部位に直接注射します。
we can put special drugs
特別な薬を入れることができます
special cells
特別な細胞
Follow this water to directly hit the damaged heart muscle
この水をたどって損傷した心筋を直接攻撃します。
This is the result of some of our previous research
これは私たちの以前の研究の結果です
with some patents
いくつかの特許を取得している
what you saw earlier
前に見たもの
You may not know these
あなたはこれらを知らないかもしれません
what does this mean
これは何を意味するのでしょうか
This is the name of each journal
各雑誌の名前です
These are all good journals like this
まだまだこのような良い雑誌がたくさんあります
But those are small animals
でもあれは小動物です
we are doing animal experiments
私たちは動物実験を行っています
We don't just bully mice
私たちはネズミをいじめるだけではありません
In fact, we have to bully different animals
実際、私たちはさまざまな動物をいじめなければなりません
Because different animals have different characteristics
動物によって特徴が違うので
can represent different diseases
さまざまな病気を表すことができます
Usually we start with small animals
通常、私たちは小動物から始めます
We will make the small animals bigger if they have results.
結果が出たら小動物を大きくしていきます。
Make it bigger and finally be a human
大きくなって、最後には人間になる
in our laboratory
私たちの研究室では
In the field of our heart
私たちの心の分野で
Usually we use four animals
通常は4匹の動物を使用します
Little mouse called Mouse
マウスと呼ばれる小さなネズミ
A rat named Red
レッドという名前のネズミ
A rabbit named Rabbit
ラビットという名前のウサギ
and mini pigs
そしてミニブタ
Meat pigs are one to two hundred kilograms
肉用豚は100～200キログラム
so we say mini pigs
だからミニブタって言うんです
A mouse is about 25 grams
マウスは約25グラム
Rat 250g
ラット 250g
Rabbit 2500g
ウサギ 2500g
Mini Pig 25000g
ミニブタ 25000g
come to schoolboy or schoolgirl
男子生徒または女子生徒のところに来てください
did you see anything
何かを見ましたか
You're so smart, Shi Jingwei
あなたはとても賢いです、シー・ジンウェイ
So if this represents the size of a mini pig
これがミニブタの大きさを表すとしたら
this is a rabbit
これはウサギです
this is a rat
これはネズミです
what is this
これは何ですか
Friends sitting in the back maybe you can't see clearly
後ろに座っている友達はよく見えないかもしれません
So it's not the same from childhood to adulthood
だから子供の頃から大人になるまで同じではない
because it's hard to say
言いにくいから
i'm a little mouse
私は小さなネズミです
good result
良い結果
I'm going to do a human test tomorrow
明日は人体実験をする予定です
probably won't work
大概行不通
not just like that
それだけではありません
If we were in different animals
もし私たちが違う動物だったら
we'll make it the same
私たちはそれを同じにします
Surgical ligation Blood vessels tied up
外科的結紮術 血管を縛る
human myocardial infarction
人間の心筋梗塞
It also produces a different phenomenon
また別の現象も引き起こします
For example, in terms of small animals
小動物で例えると、
where it produces a myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞を引き起こす場所
Most of them are on the outside of the left heart pose
ほとんどが左心の外側のポーズです
if it's a pig
それが豚なら
You do the same ligation
あなたも同じ結紮をします
where it produces a myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞を引き起こす場所
In fact, it is in two mental forms
実際、それは2つの精神形態にあります
and the place ahead
そしてその先の場所
This is exactly the same as a human
これは人間と全く同じです
So you probably can't do this
だからあなたはおそらくこれを行うことはできません
going to be a man
男になるだろう
you have to do this
あなたはこれをしなければなりません
not just like that
それだけではありません
If the same pattern of myocardial infarction
同じパターンの心筋梗塞の場合
In small animals only one
小動物では1つだけ
It only takes one week in the small family
少人数の家庭では1週間しかかかりません
it changes
それは変わる
Mind coins become so thin
マインドコインがとても薄くなってしまう
It will take two weeks
2週間かかります
Pigs are two months old
豚は生後２ヶ月です
like people
人のように
So this is actually
それで、これは実際には
really tell you
本当に教えてください
different animal patterns
さまざまな動物のパターン
In fact, there are different characteristics
実は色々な特徴があります
different needs
さまざまなニーズ
Then we use very smart
次に、非常に賢い使い方をします
The National Treasure Pig is called the Blue Feather Miniature Pig
国宝の豚は青い羽根ミニブタと呼ばれています
It has been pre-planted in Taiwan
台湾で事前に植えられています
more than 100 years
100年以上
From the time of the Japanese
日本人の時代から
has been preserved
保存されています
The Blue Feather Mini Pig
ブルーフェザーミニブタ
Mini pigs, as the name suggests, of course happened in Orchid Island
ミニブタは、その名の通り、蘭嶼で発生しました。
Produced in Orchid Island
蘭嶼産
But if you go to Lanyu today and you can't find Lanyu pigs
でも、今日蘭嶼に行って蘭嶼豚が見つからなかったら
please don't blame me
私を責めないでください
Because Lanyu no longer exists
Lanyuはもう存在しないので
Lanyu mini pigs in stock
Lanyuミニブタ入荷しました
because it doesn't grow big
大きくならないから
So it can only reach forty or fifty kilograms
つまり、40キロか50キロしかありません。
so you feed it
だからあなたはそれに餌を与えます
going to be a pig
豚になるだろう
It's useless to raise like this
このまま育てても無駄だよ
it just doesn't grow up
それは成長しないだけです
So now Lanyu is
それで今、ランユは
The pigs in Lanyu are all mixed
蘭嶼の豚はすべて混ざっている
all big ones
全部大きい
you can't find this kind of pig
こんな豚は見つからない
So luckily the Council of Agriculture kept it
幸運にも農業評議会がそれを保管してくれました
We use these Lanyu mini pigs
蘭嶼ミニブタを使用しています。
From March 2009 to the end of last year
2009年3月から昨年末まで
We are like this in Xinji Gengshe
新吉庚社ではこんな感じです
Take the mini pig for our animal model
動物モデルとしてミニブタを取り上げます
We made a total of 297 pigs
合計297匹の豚を作りました
The meeting is like saying that I am not in Tainan now
この会議は、私が今台南にいないと言っているようなものです
I'm in Taiwan
私は台湾にいます
We use different control groups
さまざまなコントロールグループを使用します
Either Xinji Terrier Society or treatment
Xinji Terrier Society または治療のいずれか
its death
その死
The whole surgical factor is still very dangerous
外科的要素全体が依然として非常に危険です
Its overall mortality rate is about 4.4%.
全体の死亡率は約 4.4% です。
Probably the best result in the world
おそらく世界最高の結果
Then our first study is to simulate
次に、最初の研究はシミュレーションです。
How to use the pig model to do clinical
ブタモデルを臨床に使用する方法
How do we do cell therapy
細胞治療はどのように行うのか
The first study we did was to grind the pig down
私たちが行った最初の研究は豚を粉砕することでした
Come on, whether it's a pig or a monkey I used to make
さあ、私が作った豚でも猿でも
Or treat us all like human beings
あるいは、私たち全員を人間として扱ってください
Has its own house suite
専用のハウススイートあり
It has its own operating room
専用の手術室があります
It has its own anesthesiologist doing it
専任の麻酔科医が担当しています
They are treated exactly the same as people
彼らは人間とまったく同じように扱われます
Then after we grind down the pig
それから豚を挽いてから
we take its marrow
私たちはその骨髄を採取します
Take ten CC of bone marrow
骨髄を10CC採取する
enough cells
十分な細胞
Why? Because we take this bone marrow out
なぜかというと、この骨髄を取り出すからです。
We extract its monocytosphere cells
その単球球細胞を抽出します
Then mix with our rice fiber water glue
次に、当社のライスファイバー水接着剤を混ぜます。
Then hit the damaged heart muscle
そして損傷した心筋を攻撃する
These cells do not escape
これらの細胞は逃げません
If you only play cells
セルだけをプレイする場合
Hit it in and it's gone
入力すると消えてしまいます
So in America, abroad, even in Taiwan
アメリカでも、海外でも、台湾でも
If you only make cells for clinical trials
臨床試験用の細胞だけを作る場合
How much bone marrow do you draw from the patient
患者からどれくらいの量の骨髄を採取しますか
so you know what?
それで、何を知っていますか？
To 1200CC is easy to say
1200CCまでは言うのは簡単です
But patients turn on you like this
でも患者はこうやってあなたに反感を抱きます
because you scored
あなたが得点したから
get a lot of cells
細胞をたくさん採取する
Most of them don't see it
彼らのほとんどはそれを見ていない
just stay there a little bit
少しだけそこにいてください
to see a little effect
少しでも効果を実感するために
We only need to pump 10CC
10CCをポンピングするだけで済みます
Because our cells don't run away
私たちの細胞は逃げないから
Wherever you type it is there
どこに入力してもそこにあります
So it will be better
それでもっと良くなるよ
We found that the practice
私たちが発見した実践は、
One month after the rent is completed
レンタル完了後1ヶ月後
We I just said two months
さっき2ヶ月って言ったけど
only one month here
ここでたったの1ヶ月
please don't blame me
私を責めないでください
Because we're doing rental Starlet for the first time and say
レンタルスターレットを初めてやると言うので
We don't have much experience ourselves
私たち自身もあまり経験がありません
so we don't know we have to wait two months
だから2ヶ月も待たなければならないとは知りませんでした
we'll just do it for a month
1ヶ月だけやります
but luckily
しかし幸運にも
It will be good in a month
1ヶ月もすれば良くなるよ
We make Zhu Ye the Xingdao tube
私たちは朱葉を星島管にします
to see how his heart works
彼の心臓がどのように機能するかを見るために
just found out
たった今わかった
If we only have to use the water glue of this rice
このお米の水糊だけを使えば
after going in
入った後
Although Zhu's contractile function is not better
朱さんの収縮機能は良くありませんが、
But the flexibility of the chapters is better
ただし、章の柔軟性は優れています
Because his pen won't get thinner
彼のペンは細くならないから
If we only play cells
セルだけをプレイするなら
His contraction function will help a little
彼の収縮機能が少しは役に立つだろう
But it doesn't help the chapter function
しかし、それは章の機能には役立ちません
because he can protect
彼は守れるから
Protect the myocardium and reduce his necrosis a little
心筋を保護し、壊死を少し軽減します
But things will still get thinner
しかし、物事はまだ薄くなります
When we combine this hydrogel with bone marrow cells
このハイドロゲルを骨髄細胞と組み合わせると
when playing together
一緒に遊んでいるとき
I can make his heart at the same time
同時に彼の心を作ることができます
Both porosity and porosity function have become better
気孔率と気孔率機能の両方が向上しました
why?
なぜ？
because if we take this cell
なぜなら、この細胞を取ると
Use the software of Red Silver Light to go
Red Silver Light のソフトウェアを使用して移動します
to feed it
それを養うために
those cells will glow
それらの細胞は光るでしょう
Then these cells follow our hydrogel
その後、これらの細胞はヒドロゲルに続きます
after hitting the heart
心臓を打った後
a month later
一ヶ月後
we can still see him
私たちはまだ彼を見ることができます
Many are still in the heart
今も心の中にたくさんの人がいる
So because the cells don't run away
細胞が逃げないから
So it will work better
それでもっとうまくいくだろう
Then we learned
それから私たちは学びました
one month is not enough
1ヶ月では足りない
so we just do it longer
だから私たちはそれをもっと長くするだけです
do it for three months
3ヶ月やってみろよ
It turned out that after three months
3か月後に判明したのは、
If only cell
セルだけなら
One month he helped the systolic function
1か月間、彼は収縮機能を助けました
gone in two months
2ヶ月で消えた
if water glue
水性接着剤の場合
His heart's systolic function isn't helping
心臓の収縮機能が役に立っていない
But loose function can last
しかし、緩んだ機能は持続することができます
three months no problem
3ヶ月なら問題ない
Do two Ken love each other?
二人のケンは愛し合っていますか?
Combining the two gives
2 つを組み合わせると、
long time three months
長時間三個月
to three months later
3ヶ月後まで
Both can have a greater effect on the function of the heart
心臓の機能に大きな影響を与える可能性があります
Protect
保護
why
なぜ
Because our water degrades very slowly
私たちの水は非常にゆっくりと劣化するため、
You know we often use some
私たちがよく使うのはご存知ですか？
Absorbable sutures to heal the wound
風や傷用の吸収性縫合糸
you don't have to guess the line
ラインを推測する必要はありません
It each a different absorbable thread
それぞれ異なる吸収糸です
Its degradation rate is different
劣化速度は様々です
If it's faster, you want it to degrade as soon as possible
高速な場合は、できるだけ早く劣化させる必要があります。
It takes a long time and you hope it doesn't degrade too early
長い時間がかかるので、あまり早く劣化しないことを願っています
Our materials will take 3 to 4 months
材料の準備には3〜4か月かかります
3 to 4 months after entering
入社後3～4ヶ月程度
It will be completely degraded by the plant heart
植物の心臓によって完全に分解されます
So as it degrades
それで劣化するにつれて
it will attract
それは引き寄せるだろう
It turns out that the cells in the own strain
自身の株の細胞が
run to where we hit
ぶつかったところまで走る
generate more positive
よりポジティブなものを生み出す
more blood vessels
より多くの血管
So mind coins don't get so thin
だからマインドコインはそんなに薄くならない
This is what we use
これが私たちが使っているものです
HPLC flutter analyzer to quantify the results
結果を定量化するための HPLC フラッター アナライザー
the next question is
次の質問は
what we did before
私たちが前にやったこと
To be honest, I really don't have much experience.
正直に言うと、私はあまり経験がありません。
Although they all publish good articles like this
どれもこのような良い記事を掲載していますが、
But what we don't know much about
しかし、私たちがあまり知らないこと
What we did before was pigs tying up the big blood vessels
私たちは豚が太い血管を縛っていました
Myocardial infarction is involved, get treatment quickly
心筋梗塞の可能性があるので早めに治療を受けてください
But will it be like this clinically?
しかし臨床的にもそうなるのでしょうか？
Is there a time when a patient with myocardial infarction runs ahead of you?
心筋梗塞の患者さんが先を行く時ってありますか？
Just say hurry up and call me, it's impossible
急いで電話してください、それは不可能です
So what we want to know is to say
そこで私たちが知りたいのは、
Such treatment if after myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞後の場合はこのような治療
Do treatment right away or wait a day or wait four days
すぐに治療を行うか、1 日待つか、4 日待つか
even wait seven days to do it
それをするのに7日待っても
Will it also work
それも効くのかな
It's all very simple
すべてとてもシンプルです
It's all one sentence, but it takes a long time to do
全部一文だけど、やるのに時間がかかる
cost a lot of money
多額のお金がかかる
This is Zhang Mingyao and one of us
こちらは張明耀と私たちの一員です
Ph.D.
博士号
He's at a muscle growth company in the south now
彼は今、南部の筋肉増強会社に勤めています
treat it like a baby
赤ちゃんのように扱う
he did many things
彼はたくさんのことをした
he found out
彼は見つけた
If our treatment after myocardial infarction in pigs
ブタの心筋梗塞後の治療の場合
do it right away or one day or four days
すぐに行うか、1 日または 4 日以内に行うか
It will make the pig's heart function better
豚の心臓の機能を良くする
but if you do it in seven days
でも7日以内にやれば
sorry it's too late no help
ごめんなさい、遅すぎます、仕方ありません
why is it like this
なぜこんなことになっているのか
because of myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞のため
But after that he had a big damage to his heart
しかしその後、彼は心に大きなダメージを負ってしまいました
But in the follow-up, his injury continued
しかしその後の経過観察でも彼の怪我は続いた
After waiting for a long time, his heart function is getting worse
長い間待った後、心臓の機能が悪化している
so you wait until seven days to do it
だから7日まで待ってください
His heart function has become worse
彼の心臓の機能が悪くなった
And this systemic vocal response
そしてこの全身的な音声反応は
will make your bone marrow cells worse and worse
骨髄細胞がますます悪化する可能性があります
The ability to grow blood vessels is also reduced
血管を成長させる能力も低下します
So even if you use it for healing effect
なのでヒーリング効果を狙って使っても
not so good
あまりよくない
so the sooner the better
だから早ければ早いほど良い
Well, then my dream comes again
さぁ、また夢がやってくる
If one day we can be in Taiwan
いつか台湾に行けたら
There is a treatment center like this one
こんな治療院があります
I always think that we in Taiwan should have
私たちは台湾にいるべきだといつも思っています。
To develop more sophisticated
より洗練された開発を行うために
relatively new technology
比較的新しい技術
With our good medical system
充実した医療体制で
Instead of introducing foreign countries every time
毎回外国を紹介するのではなく
imported from abroad
海外から輸入された
We should have something we develop ourselves
自分たちで開発したものを持つべきだ
Our treatments are
私たちの治療法は、
If after myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞後の場合
Do it in four days and you will have better results
4日以内にやればより良い結果が得られます
So if one day we really are
だからいつか私たちが本当にそうなったら
Taiwan can CREATE such a
台湾はそのようなものを生み出すことができる
when the treatment center
治療センターのとき
As long as the myocardial infarction is within four days
心筋梗塞発生から4日以内であれば
can fly to
に飛ぶことができます
Come to Taiwan to receive this treatment
この治療を受けるために台湾に来てください
we can give you a better prognosis
より良い予後を提供できます
It's better to walk out alive
生きて出た方が良いよ
In those four days, I could fly many laps in the Ninth Classic
この 4 日間で第 9 回クラシックを何周も飛ぶことができました
I hope one day this dream can come true
いつかこの夢が叶うことを願っています
that another interesting stardis
別の興味深いスターディス
Do we have to use nanofiber hydrogel?
ナノファイバーハイドロゲルを使用する必要がありますか?
can we use other
他のものを使用できますか
This is another Ph.D.
これは別の博士号です。
Now postdoctoral fellow Chen Jianxi Dr. Chen
現在博士研究員 Chen Jianxi チェン博士
He takes hyaluronic acid
彼はヒアルロン酸を摂取しています
this is playing every day
これは毎日遊んでいます
There are two kinds of hyaluronic acid in our clinic
当院では２種類のヒアルロン酸をご用意しております
one is knuckle
1つはナックルです
This is degradable
これは分解可能です
so it won't be long
だから長くはかからないよ
it will be degraded slowly
ゆっくりと劣化していきます
One is to hit this
1つはこれを打つことです
Do you know what you are doing?
自分が何をしているか知っていますか？
This is a glue face
これは接着面です
so it can stay longer
長く滞在できるように
We use knuckles
うちはナックルを使ってます
because we don't want it to stay for too long
あまり長く留まりたくないから
So if we take hyaluronic acid
そこでヒアルロン酸を摂取すると
with bone marrow cells
骨髄細胞を使った
Do the same for the treatment of myocardial infarction in pigs
豚の心筋梗塞の治療にも同じことをする
Treating it will also work
治療することも効果があります
Because hyaluronic acid is originally
ヒアルロン酸はもともと
Can help long-term students
長期滞在学生をサポートできる
OK
OK
again
また
Do I have to use paleo cells?
古細胞を使用する必要がありますか?
some patients are afraid
怖がる患者もいる
Whoever hears that they want to vomit ancient times will have weak feet
昔、吐きたいと聞く人は足が弱いでしょう
Although only Shi Xixi
石西だけだけど
We found out that we might be able to take peripheral blood
末梢血を採取できるかもしれないことが分かりました
Or take several generations of blood
または数世代の血液を採取する
Everyone knows we are in Taiwan
私たちが台湾にいることは誰もが知っています
We now have 100,000 tubes of several generations of blood
私たちは現在、数世代の血液が入った 100,000 本のチューブを保有しています。
stored in our cell bank
私たちの細胞バンクに保管されています
We found that in the pig mode
ブタモードでそれがわかりました
We take generations of human blood
私たちは何世代にもわたる人間の血を採取します
This is a collaboration with Dr. Huang Xiaoyuan, Princess Stone
これはプリンセスストーンの黄暁源博士とのコラボレーションです。
Take the blood of several generations
数世代の血を採取する
Mixed with Ornithium and hitting the pig's heart
オルニジウムを混ぜて豚の心臓を叩く
the cell will be repelled say
細胞は反発されるだろうと言う
We want to give anti-rejection waist
反撃腰をあげたい
I'm like an organ
私は臓器のようなものです
We found that the practice
私たちが発見した実践は、
May also help the function of the heart
心臓の機能も助ける可能性がある
So it's not just nano water
つまり、ただのナノ水ではないのです
Ornithotic acid can also
オルニトン酸はまた、
Paleo-cells
古細胞
We can also take generations of blood cells
血球を何世代にもわたって採取することもできます
can achieve good results
良い結果を達成できる
as long as the two are combined
2つが組み合わされている限り
If you only hit cells, it's useless
セルを叩くだけじゃダメだよ
It's useless to just fetch water
水汲むだけじゃダメだよ
must be combined
組み合わせる必要があります
The issue of ischemia was just mentioned
虚血の問題については先ほど触れました
parotid encephalopathy stroke
耳下腺脳症脳卒中
Cheeky Heart Myocardial Infarction
生意気なハート心筋梗塞
There will also be big problems with the cheeks and feet
頬や足にも大きな問題が発生します
This is actually such a patient
実はこんな患者さんなんです
More patients than myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞よりも患者数が多い
diabetic patient
糖尿病患者
His blood vessels will be diseased
彼の血管は病気になるだろう
will block in the end
結局ブロックするだろう
especially the lower limbs
特に下肢
So you may have heard
それで、聞いたことがあるかもしれません
Many patients with diabetes
糖尿病患者が多い
his wound won't heal
彼の傷は治らないだろう
black toes
黒いつま先
so in the end it will
だから最終的にはそうなるだろう
amputated toes one by one
足の指を一本ずつ切断
In the end the whole foot will be cut off
最後には足全体が切断されてしまいます
I have several such patients myself.
私自身にもそのような患者さんが何人かいます。
This is actually a serious problem
実はこれは深刻な問題なのです
Because more and more people with diabetes
糖尿病の人が増えているから
no medicine
薬がない
sorry
ごめん
Because of this vascular patient
この血管患者のせいで
It looks like it was eaten whole in the end.
結局丸ごと食べてしまったようです。
So we can't do bypass surgery
だからバイパス手術はできない
We can't place the price
価格は付けられません
only take medicine
薬だけを飲む
Make your blood less likely to clot
血液が固まりにくくなる
accidentally bleeding
誤って出血する
These patients are actually very poor
これらの患者は実際には非常に貧しい
In the end there is no other way
結局それ以外に道はないんだよ
just want it
ただ欲しいだけ
in this way
この上
When it comes to sick patients the main thing is to leave in the end
病気の患者に関して言えば、重要なことは最終的には去ることだ
Myocardial infarction or stroke
心筋梗塞または脳卒中
But as long as he lives long enough
しかし、彼が長生きする限り、
he will be like this
彼はこうなるだろう
So is there any way we can get through
それで、私たちが乗り越えられる方法はありますか？
The way we treat
私たちの治療方法
Similar treatment modalities for myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞に対する同様の治療法
can help these patients
これらの患者を助けることができる
Let him not be like this one day
いつか彼がこんな風にならないようにしましょう
This is actually a very important
これは実はとても重要なことなのですが、
This is actually the first clinical trial we're going to do
実はこれが私たちが行う初めての臨床試験です
We started talking with the Ministry of Health and Welfare three years ago
3年前から厚生省と話し合いを始めました。
Department of Health
保健省
FDA
FDA
Apply for a clinical trial
臨床試験を申請する
Then start because when you applied
申請したときから開始します
Although we have published a bunch of articles
たくさんの記事を公開してきましたが、
not bad article
悪くない記事
but they're still scared
でも彼らはまだ怖がっている
because never done
一度もやったことがないので
No one in the world has done it
世界中で誰もやったことがない
So I explained that we have a lot of homework to do
それで私は、やるべき宿題がたくさんあると説明しました
Let's just do the same thing obediently
素直に同じことしようよ
It's been three years now
もう3年も経ったんですね
we haven't been fully approved to say
私たちが言うことは完全に承認されていません
can do this clinical trial
この臨床試験を行うことができます
But this year should be the last time
でも今年が最後になるはずだ
should do this year
今年はやるべきだ
Because it's really the last step
本当に最後のステップだから
We want our hyaluronic acid and water cells
ヒアルロン酸と水分細胞が欲しい
Or the treatment of hyaluronic acid combined with blood dripping cells
または、血液滴下細胞と組み合わせたヒアルロン酸の治療
can start to help our patients
患者を助け始めることができる
Can keep it from being amputated one day like this
これでいつか切断されるのを防ぐことができる
this
これ
The idea is actually very simple, just like before
以前と同じように、アイデアは実際には非常にシンプルです
Hyaluronic acid itself will help grow blood vessels
ヒアルロン酸自体が血管の成長を助ける
After the cells of this water enter
この水の細胞が入った後
won't run away right away
すぐには逃げません
So combining these two treatments
したがって、これら 2 つの治療法を組み合わせると、
May be able to grow better blood vessels
より良い血管を成長させることができるかもしれない
to help patients with these peripheral vascular components
これらの末梢血管コンポーネントを持つ患者を助けるため
We did this more than two years ago
これは2年以上前に行いました
Have already applied to the NRPD program
すでにNRPDプログラムに申請している
I have been stopping there waiting for the Ministry of Health and Welfare to say OK
厚生省がOKを出すのを待ってそこに止まっています。
We will
私達はします
In National Taiwan University Hospital and City University Hospital
国立台湾大学病院および市立大学病院内
Start our first issue
最初の問題を開始します
Phase II clinical trial
第II相臨床試験
hope
希望
this
これ
Can do it this year
今年はできるかな
let us
私たちにさせて
could help these patients earlier
これらの患者をより早く助けることができる
because even today every day
なぜなら今日も毎日
There are 19,000 patients in Taiwan
台湾の患者数は19,000人
at risk of amputation
切断の危険にさらされている
so we just have to do it earlier
だからもっと早くやればいいだけだ
maybe save a few legs
もしかしたら数脚を節約できるかもしれない
One leg represents a family
一本の足は家族を表します
not a leg
脚ではない
The last thing I want to introduce to you is
最後にご紹介したいのは、
Wear a study of stem cells
幹細胞の研究を身につける
ok we go here now
わかりました、今ここに行きます
We can now wear stem cells
幹細胞を身につけることができるようになりました
Or a type of cells called IPS cells
またはIPS細胞と呼ばれる細胞の一種
induced pluripotent stem cells
人工多能性幹細胞
That is, the Japanese mountain raw rice
つまり日本の山生米
called what he did get
彼が得たものをそう呼ぶ
This study of the Bill Award
ビル賞に関するこの研究
So it is not a problem to become a New Territories cell
したがって、新界細胞になることは問題ではありません
But now we want to deal with this matter
しかし今、私たちはこの問題に取り組みたいと思っています
good
良い
Take cells to the New Territories to help these patients
これらの患者を助けるために細胞を新領域に連れて行きます
The results of more than ten years of clinical trials
10年以上にわたる臨床試験の結果
Today there are more than 10,000 patients worldwide
現在、世界中で10,000人以上の患者がいます
have received cell therapy
細胞療法を受けている
Mostly own bone marrow cells
ほとんどが自分自身の骨髄細胞
or peripheral blood cells
または末梢血細胞
to treat his heart disease
彼の心臓病を治療するために
Of course mainly abroad
もちろん主に海外
America Most Europe
アメリカのほとんどのヨーロッパ
over the past ten years
この10年
Those 10,000 patients are registered
その10,000人の患者が登録されている
the unregistered one
未登録のもの
We didn't know it was registered
登録されているとは知りませんでした
More than 10,000 patients have received this
10,000人以上の患者がこれを受けています
autologous cell therapy
自己細胞療法
After more than ten years of such clinical experimental research
このような臨床実験研究を10年以上続けた結果、
come to two conclusions
2つの結論に達する
First cell therapy to treat heart disease is safe
心臓病を治療する初の細胞療法は安全
You don't have to worry about its side effects
副作用を心配する必要はありません
The second conclusion is cell therapy to treat heart disease
2番目の結論は、心臓病を治療するための細胞療法です
is invalid
無効です
or only slightly
あるいはほんの少しだけ
or only a short-term effect
または短期的な効果のみ
The main reason is what I just said
主な理由は今言ったことです
Called in and disappeared
呼び出されて消えた
But there's still something to do
でも、まだやるべきことがある
A lot of things just develop slowly
多くのことはゆっくりと発展していきます
Then one of them is France
そしてそのうちの1つはフランスです
Feliz Mahlerchet
フェリス・マーレルシェット
a friend
友達
The clinical trials they did ten years ago
10年前に彼らが行った臨床試験
made nine patients
9人の患者を作った
Take his skeletal muscle cells
彼の骨格筋細胞を採取してください
stem cells from his skeletal muscle
彼の骨格筋からの幹細胞
differentiate it into muscle cells
筋肉細胞に分化させる
into his own heart
自分の心に打ち込む
Because skeletal muscle cells are very good
骨格筋細胞は非常に優れているため、
Our heart muscle regenerates poorly
私たちの心筋は再生が不十分です
i just said
私はちょうど言いました
But our skeletal muscle regeneration ability is very good
しかし、私たちの骨格筋の再生能力は非常に優れています。
If you work hard to perform today
今日頑張ってパフォーマンスしたら
Hit hard and I may die a lot of cells
強く叩くとたくさんの細胞が死ぬかもしれない
But I also stimulated a lot of skeletal muscle stem cells
しかし、私はまた、多くの骨格筋幹細胞を刺激しました
to regenerate my skeletal muscles
骨格筋を再生するために
So these muscles are very good at regenerative
したがって、これらの筋肉は再生能力が非常に優れています
And it has a great advantage that
そして、それには大きな利点があります。
It is not afraid of hypoxia and ischemia
低酸素や虚血を恐れません
If we compare skeletal muscle cells and cardiac muscle cells today
今、骨格筋細胞と心筋細胞を比べてみると
grow together in a hypoxic environment
低酸素環境で一緒に成長する
In less than a day, these cardiomyocytes are probably dead.
おそらく 1 日も経たないうちに、これらの心筋細胞は死滅してしまうでしょう。
Skeletal muscle cells are still alive
骨格筋細胞はまだ生きています
Can live for more than a week no problem
1週間以上生きても問題ない
is autologous
自己由来です
muscles everywhere
どこにでもある筋肉
so you'd want to say
だからあなたは言いたいでしょう
how nice
なんと素晴らしいことでしょう
There is no better source of cells than this
これより優れた細胞源はありません
Why are you doing stem cells with him?
なぜ彼と一緒に幹細胞をやっているのですか？
But from early clinical events it was found that
しかし、初期の臨床事象から次のことが判明しました。
These nine patients took their own skeletal muscle myocytes
これら 9 人の患者は自分自身の骨格筋細胞を採取しました
after hitting the heart
心臓を打った後
There are five bars to install the electric shock device
感電装置を取り付けるバーは5本あります。
because it creates dysphoria
それは不快感を引き起こすからです
that's what i just said
それが私が今言ったことです
The two cells cannot combine
2 つのセルを結合することはできません
Shrink and jump together
縮んで一緒にジャンプ
Because its electrical conduction mechanism is different
電気伝導の仕組みが違うから
even if it's your own
たとえそれが自分のものであっても
So the electrical conduction to the skeletal muscle
したがって、骨格筋への電気伝導は
When it reaches the myocardium, it hits the wall.
心筋に到達すると壁にぶつかります。
It won't pass, so there will be arrhythmia
通らないから不整脈が起こる
So obviously this won't work
したがって、明らかにこれは機能しません
Another relatively new study
もう一つの比較的新しい研究
This is Xinyatu's collaborator
こちらはシンヤトゥの協力者です
It's my big brother named Chuck Murray
チャック・マレーという名の私の兄です
He is wearing stem cells in the United States
彼は米国で幹細胞を装着している
Become the most famous group of mental cells
最も有名な精神細胞のグループになる
They published an article over a year ago
彼らは1年以上前に記事を公開しました
It is to take people's wearing stem cells
それは人々の身に着けている幹細胞を摂取することです
differentiate it into cardiomyocytes
それを心筋細胞に分化させる
Then beat it into the monkey's heart
それなら猿の心臓に叩きつけろ
they first discovered that
彼らはそれを最初に発見した
can be inside the heart of the long class
長いクラスの中心部にいることもできます
To grow human brain tissue
人間の脳組織を成長させるには
this is a big big breakthrough
これは大きな大きな進歩です
But they also found that arrhythmia
しかし彼らは不整脈も発見した
Why is the heart rate irregular?
心拍数が不規則になるのはなぜですか?
The same thing, human brain cells are the same as monkey brain cells
同じこと、人間の脳細胞もサルの脳細胞も同じです
Of course they won't shrink and dance together.
もちろん縮こまらず一緒に踊ります。
so how to decide this question
では、この質問をどう判断するか
is an important question to decide
決定すべき重要な質問です
OK, let me introduce our two technologies quickly.
さて、私たちの 2 つのテクノロジーを簡単に紹介しましょう。
That is, we use the technology of electric imitation silk and magnetic field nano
つまり、電気模造シルクと磁場ナノの技術を使用しています。
That is to say, we go to spray electricity to imitate silk
つまり、シルクを模倣して電気を噴射しに行きます
spray it and it will run around
スプレーすると走り回ります
But we use magnetic fields to structure
しかし、私たちは磁場を使って構造を構築します
The position of controlling the running of electric imitation silk is adjusted one by one
電動模造絹の走行を制御する位置を一つ一つ調整
is permuted
並べ替えられています
like this
このような
Then the control group and the experiment have a control group
次に、対照グループと実験には対照グループがあります
The control group is to spray it out and let it run by itself
対照群はスプレーして勝手に走らせる
So it produces this kind of running around
したがって、このような走りが発生します
such a random
そんなランダムな
The nanofiber
ナノファイバー
Then we make it a patch for the new machine
次に、それを新しいマシン用のパッチにします
So one is permutation and combination and the other is not.
つまり、1 つは順列と組み合わせであり、もう 1 つはそうではありません。
Then we found that when we put the new machine cells
そして、新しいマシンセルを設置すると、
In the two new tents with vascular endothelial cells
血管内皮細胞に関する2つの新しい報告において
most important cell
最も重要な細胞
A patch like this that is aligned in this arrangement
こんな配置で並んだこんなパッチ
it will grow out one by one
一つ一つ成長していきます
Just like the mobile organization of our new account
新しいアカウントのモバイル構成と同じように
If you put it on the back of the random row
ランダムな列の一番後ろに置くと
its own random run around
独自のランダムな実行
Then we use a relatively new one called an atomic force microscope
次に、原子間力顕微鏡と呼ばれる比較的新しいものを使用します。
very nanometer very thin
非常にナノメートルの非常に薄い
to detect its contraction
その収縮を検出するために
you can find out that
あなたはそれを知ることができます
If you compare cardiomyocytes with endothelial cells
心筋細胞と内皮細胞を比較すると
well aligned in this
これでうまく調整されています
When the surface of the myocardial patch
心筋パッチの表面が傷つくと、
it will shrink better
良く縮みます
Jump faster and more regularly
より速く、より定期的にジャンプする
Then we put this myocardial patch into
次に、この心筋パッチを
Most of the MI-colored outside go
MI色の外側のほとんどが行きます
You have to line up, you can't line up some guides
並ばないといけないけど、ガイドによっては並ばないこともある
Can't line up vertically
縦に並べられない
We need to compare that fiber with the fiber of our heart
その繊維と私たちの心の繊維を比較する必要があります
The angle must be right and not crooked.
角度は直角であり、曲がっていてはなりません。
Put it on after it's done
終わったら装着してください
Two months later, I will go for an ultrasound of the heart
2か月後、心臓の超音波検査を受けに行きます
will find out that
それが分かるだろう
This is better
これの方が良い
Such myocardial patch
このような心筋パッチ
It will greatly help the function of the heart
心臓の働きを大きく助けてくれる
do cardiac catheterization
心臓カテーテル検査をする
We can also do cardiac catheterization in mice
マウスの心臓カテーテル検査も可能です
The same is true for the systolic function of the heart
心臓の収縮機能にも同じことが当てはまります
It will be better with the sparse expansion function
スパース展開機能を使えばさらに良くなる
It will even reduce the area of ​​myocardial necrosis
心筋壊死の領域も縮小します
and two months later
そして2ヶ月後
This is the cardiac patch we implanted
これが私たちが移植した心臓パッチです
upper cardiomyocytes
心筋細胞
it will follow
それは続きます
The structure of the scheming of the normal heart is
正常な心臓の仕組みは、
direction is exactly the same
方向性が全く同じです
So when we take this heart out
だからこの心を取り出すと
Give it a software that covers ions
イオンをカバーするソフトウェアを提供する
and then look at the way it conducts electricity
それから電気がどのように流れるかを調べてください
will find that such
そのようなことがわかります
Scheming cells in permutations
順列の心臓細胞
send it up
それを送ってください
Such a scheming patch
そんな陰謀パッチ
will allow our electrical conduction
私たちの電気伝導を可能にします
From this scheming patch
この陰謀パッチから
It can be transmitted to a normal heart
正常な心臓にも伝わる
MOOS passed smoothly
MOOSは順調に通過しました
If you put it in that messy long
そんなに長い時間入れたら
the fiber
繊維
it produces a heartbeat
それは心臓の鼓動を生み出す
This is also an easy study
これも簡単な勉強です
the other one
別のもの
embryonic stem cells
ES細胞
islet pluripotent stem cells
膵島多能性幹細胞
can become heart cells
心臓の細胞になることができる
Can be used for many purposes
さまざまな目的に使用できます
Can do cell therapy
細胞治療ができる
can do drug development
創薬ができる
Can be used to explore the mechanism of disease
病気のメカニズムを調べるために使用できる
But from embryonic stem cells
しかし、胚性幹細胞からは
or IPS stem cells
またはIPS幹細胞
cardiomyocytes
心筋細胞
It's also the cell of the embryonic heart
胎児の心臓の細胞でもある
not like our normal mature cardiomyocytes
私たちの通常の成熟した心筋細胞とは異なります
So the two are still different
だから二人はまだ違うんだよ
Although in theory
理論上ではありますが
You know it's very difficult for us to get cardiomyocytes
心筋細胞を入手するのは非常に難しいことはご存知でしょう
It may be difficult for you to tell patients
患者さんに伝えるのは難しいかもしれません
sorry i want to study you
ごめんなさい、あなたのことを勉強したいです
why do you have this disease
なぜこの病気になったのですか
Cut a piece of your heart and let me do some research, okay?
あなたの心臓の一部を切り取って、ちょっと調べさせてください、いいですか？
Let me cut a piece of your head out
あなたの頭の一部を切り取らせてください
Why don't you just cut it into pieces?
それを細かく切ってみませんか？
patients probably won't accept
患者はおそらく受け入れないだろう
But today if I tell you
でも今日言ったら
we have a technology
私たちには技術があります
I just want to draw two CCs of blood with you
あなたと一緒に血を2CC描きたいだけです
I can grow your embryonic stem cells
あなたの胚性幹細胞を育てることができます
I can differentiate it into cardiomyocytes
心筋細胞に分別できる
differentiate into nerve cells
神経細胞に分化する
differentiate into liver cells
肝細胞に分化する
to do research
研究をする
do you want to
あなたは＿＿したいですか
Probably most people will nod and touch to see
おそらくほとんどの人がうなずいたり触ったりするでしょう。
cut a piece of heart you don't want
いらない心の一部を切り取る
If you draw two CCs of blood, you will probably accept it.
2CC採血すればおそらく受け入れてくれるでしょう。
This is the purpose of our technology
これが私たちの技術の目的です
I will continue to say this
これからもこう言い続けます
mouse embryonic stem cells
マウス胚性幹細胞
we made a
私たちはを作りました
gene transfer
遺伝子導入
The benefits of embryonic stem cells are
ES細胞の利点は次のとおりです。
it differentiates into the body
それは体に分化します
more than two hundred cells
200以上の細胞
Including what we usually dare not be cut
普段はあえてカットできないものも含めて
cells of the brain
脳の細胞
Heart muscle cells Liver cells
心筋細胞 肝細胞
We can all use embryonic stem cells
ES細胞は誰でも使える
Or IPSL differentiates it
または IPSL がそれを区別します
Okay, so we did a genetic change.
さて、遺伝子組み換えを行いました。
Let this embryonic stem cell angle
この胚性幹細胞に角度を付けてみましょう
it becomes cardiomyocytes
心筋細胞になります
it will glow green
緑色に光ります
So we can use a machine
それで機械を使えるようになります
cell separator
セルセパレーター
purify these cells
これらの細胞を浄化する
then we found these
それから私たちはこれらを見つけました
green cardiomyocytes
緑色の心筋細胞
it is immature
それは未熟です
But if it compares with vascular endothelial cells
しかし、血管内皮細胞と比較すると
grow together grow together
一緒に成長する 一緒に成長する
it'll start on day one
それは初日から始まります
start after day three
3日目以降に開始
Line up one by one
一人ずつ並びます
like our base fresh tail
私たちのベースのフレッシュテールのように
And it has a better base fresh tail structure
より優れたベースと新鮮なテール構造を備えています。
then you just ask
それからあなたはただ尋ねます
what endothelial cells do
内皮細胞は何をしているのか
original endothelial cells
元の内皮細胞
it can be released
それは解放できる
it can help this
それはこれを助けることができます
produce some tiny tiny
小さな小さなものを生み出す
RNA
RNA
called microRNA
マイクロRNAと呼ばれる
So when we put
それで、私たちが置くとき
Find these four important
重要な 4 つを見つけてください
The MICRO-RNA we want is called 125B199A21222
私たちが必要とする MICRO-RNA は 125B199A21222 と呼ばれます
Treat these four MICRO-RNAs as drugs
これら 4 つの MICRO-RNA を薬として扱う
to add to this immature scheming cell
この未熟な陰謀細胞にさらに加えるために
it becomes more mature
それはより成熟します
And these four MICRO-RNA
そしてこの4つのMICRO-RNA
Their mechanism of action has a specific...
彼らの作用機序には特有のものがあります...
our MICRO-RNA this tiny nuclear soup nucleic acid
私たちのMICRO-RNAはこの小さな核スープの核酸です
It usually has hundreds of mechanisms of action
通常、何百もの作用メカニズムがあります
There are 10,000 to 20,000 voices
ボイス数は10,000～20,000
But every MICRO-RNA
しかし、すべてのMICRO-RNAは
It has a different mechanism of action
異なる作用機序を持っています
It's funny that the four of us
4人だと面白いですね
it actually has the same goal
実は同じ目標を持っています
the same mechanism of action
同じ作用機序
This gene is called ERB4
この遺伝子はERB4と呼ばれます
This gene was found in early Tibet
この遺伝子は初期チベットで発見された
A gene important in embryonic development
胚の発生に重要な遺伝子
But once you mature and become an adult
でも、成長して大人になったら、
The gene is gone
遺伝子が消えた
it doesn't express
それは表現しない
We found that our MICRO-RNA
私たちのMICRO-RNAは、
is acting on this gene
この遺伝子に作用している
So when we directly in this scheming cell
それで、私たちがこの陰謀を企てる部屋に直接入ったとき、
When this gene suppresses it
この遺伝子が抑制すると
It will grow more mature myocardial tissue
より成熟した心筋組織が成長します
not just in mice
マウスに限らず
It's the same in humans
それは人間でも同じです
human embryonic stem cells
ヒト胚性幹細胞
become cardiomyocytes
心筋細胞になる
It also started as an embryonic entity
それはまた、初期の実体として始まります
But after the four of us
でも4人になった後は
After treatment with micro-RNA drugs
マイクロRNA医薬品による治療後
It also grows more mature cardiomyocytes
また、より成熟した心筋細胞も成長します
its electrical conduction
その電気伝導
The amplitude of the image jump
画像ジャンプの振幅
like mature cardiomyocytes
成熟した心筋細胞のような
So this is one of our models
これは私たちのモデルの1つです
This is our newest
これは私たちの最新のものです
A newly graduated doctoral student named Keith
キースという名前の新卒博士課程学生
Because this study is in the Sale Report
この調査は販売レポートに掲載されているため、
is his cover story
彼のカバーストーリーです
So if you notice the news
それで、このニュースに気づいたら
It seems to be noisy
騒がしいようです
It's so loud
とてもうるさいです
But everyone seems to be very interested in it
でも、みんなとても興味があるようです
so everyone asks
だからみんなが尋ねる
where is your student
あなたの生徒はどこですか
we are going to visit him
私たちは彼を訪ねるつもりです
Our model is through
私たちのモデルは完成しました
immature embryonic stem cells
未熟な胚性幹細胞
derived cardiomyocytes
派生心筋細胞
cultured with endothelial cells
内皮細胞とともに培養
It will stimulate these four chronic
これら4つの慢性的な刺激を与えます。
It will always be ERBV4 this gene
この遺伝子は常に ERBV4 になります
Let immature scheming become mature scheming
未熟な策略を成熟した策略にしましょう
and interestingly
そして興味深いことに
Such a heart cell
そんな心臓細胞
We only need one treatment after giving this drug
この薬を投与した後、必要な治療は 1 回だけです
to 60 days later
60日後まで
This accumulation of tissue between each cell
各細胞間の組織のこの蓄積
This is to prevent mental disorder
精神障害を防ぐためです
it can grow very well
とてもよく成長することができます
So these cells can be used for great purposes
したがって、これらの細胞は素晴らしい目的に使用できます
so as it may generate
生成できるように
Such a large potential application
このような大きな潜在的なアプリケーション
With the support of NRPV
NRPVの支援により
Just now the vice president mentioned
先ほど副大統領もおっしゃいましたが、
We are different units from Taiwan for stem cells
私たちは台湾とは異なる幹細胞部門です
some good friends some seniors
仲の良い友達もいるし、先輩もいる
join together
一緒に参加する
we have a goal
私たちには目標があります
I just hope to help stem cells in Taiwan
台湾の幹細胞を助けたいと願うばかりです
do something
何かをする
what to do
何をすべきか
we set up a core facility
中核施設を設立しました
Then come to help clinical doctors in Taiwan
それから台湾の臨床医師を助けに来てください
Want to do this Yushima sex more adult
もっと大人な湯島セックスしたい
Stem Cell IPSL
幹細胞IPSL
to help them do
彼らが行うのを助けるために
because it takes a lot of time
とても時間がかかるので
a lot of energy
たくさんのエネルギー
It's not easy to do and it even costs a lot of money
それは簡単なことではありませんし、多額の費用もかかります。
We hope that such a coalition can be produced
私たちはそのような連合が生まれることを願っています
Help Taiwan do this
台湾のこれを支援する
iPS stem cells
iPS的乾細胞
The goal is to have it by the end of next year
目標は来年末までの完成です
We're going to make 100
100個作るつもりです
Stem cells made from patients with 100 diseases
100の病気の患者から作られた幹細胞
and store it in
そしてそれを保存します
The Food Industry Institute invites people from all over Taiwan to do research
食品産業研究所は台湾全土から研究者を招待しています
can apply for
申請できる
it will make a big difference
それは大きな違いを生むだろう
Because these iPS
なぜなら、これらのiPSは
Well-intentioned and fruitful stem cells
善意と実りをもたらす幹細胞
like i just said
先ほど言ったように
I don't need to take yours and cut your heart
あなたの心を奪ってあなたの心を切る必要はない
no need to cut your head off
頭を切り落とす必要はない
No need to cut your liver
肝臓を切る必要はない
I just need to draw two cc of blood
2cc採血するだけです
I can turn it into your own stem cells
あなた自身の幹細胞に変えることができます
and differentiate it into these cells
そしてこれらの細胞に分化します
for disease research
病気の研究のために
for drug screening
薬物スクリーニング用
for personalized medicine
個別化医療に向けて
so one day
それである日
Now it's slowly starting to happen
今、それがゆっくりと起こり始めています
This technology will develop to
この技術は次のように発展します
if there is a patient
患者がいるなら
he has cancer
彼は癌を患っている
he has to do chemo
彼は化学療法をしなければならない
But we know that many chemotherapy drugs
しかし、多くの化学療法薬が
he will be cardiotoxic
彼は心中毒になるだろう
Many clinical patients
多くの臨床患者
After chemotherapy for his cancer
癌の化学療法後
Cancer shrinks or even disappears
がんは縮小するか、消滅することもあります
But the patient passed away with heart failure.
しかし患者は心不全で亡くなった。
this is a serious problem
これは深刻な問題です
If we have these technologies
これらの技術があれば
Applications to Personalized Medicine
個別化医療への応用
patient today
今日の患者
we know you have cancer
私たちはあなたが癌であることを知っています
One day you may have to do chemotherapy drugs
いつか化学療法をしなければならないかもしれない
let me borrow it from you first
まずはあなたから借りさせてください
Take two CG blood first
まず CG の血液を 2 つ採取します
give us two months
2ヶ月待ってください
even shorter time
さらに短い時間で
i can make your
私はあなたのものを作ることができます
IPS stem cells
IPS的乾細胞
we can make your cardiomyocytes
私たちはあなたの心筋細胞を作ることができます
your liver cells
あなたの肝細胞
your nerve cells
あなたの神経細胞
Then let's test it for you
それでは、あなたのためにテストしてみましょう
What drugs are available in hospitals now?
現在病院で利用できる薬は何ですか?
Which of these medicines is best for you
これらの薬のうちどれがあなたに最適ですか
The least toxic and the best
毒性が最も少なく、最高のもの
so we can talk to you
それであなたと話せます
I'm sorry, you can't take this medicine.
申し訳ありませんが、この薬は服用できません。
But it's best for you with this medicine
でも、この薬を飲むのが一番いいよ
If we say we are in Taiwan
ここが台湾だと言ったら
Especially through Taiwan BioBank
特に台湾バイオバンクを通じて
Taiwan Biobank
台湾バイオバンク
this one in Taiwan
これは台湾にある
Now we're doing this
今、私たちはこれをやっています
200,000 patients draw blood
20万人の患者が採血
Then do research every 5 years
その後、5年ごとに調査を行う
inside this database
このデータベース内で
We can choose the most
私たちは最も多くのものを選ぶことができます
most representative genotype
最も代表的な遺伝子型
then each of us
それから私たち一人一人が
make it all IPSL
すべてをIPSLにする
save it all
すべて保存してください
These 50 people can represent
この 50 人が代表できる
More than 70% of the people in Taiwan
台湾国民の70％以上が
His genotype will be very similar
彼の遺伝子型は非常に似ているでしょう
So one day if we were to use him as a representative
だからいつか彼を代表として使うとしたら
even take him
彼を連れて行っても
Differentiate it into cells for cell therapy
細胞治療用の細胞に分化させる
as long as people in Taiwan
台湾の人々がいる限り
you have a 70% chance
70％の確率で
can be found inside these 50 stem cells
これらの50個の幹細胞内で見つけることができます
with you can use
あなたと一緒に使用できます
Can be used as a cell chair
携帯椅子としても使えます
like an organ chair
オルガン椅子のような
This will have a big impact
これは大きな影響を及ぼします
even say that we can put this
これを置くことができるとさえ言う
Although only 50
たったの50ですが
But it can represent 70% of
しかし、それは 70% を表す可能性があります。
Taiwanese genotyped cells
台湾の遺伝子型別細胞
turn it into cardiomyocytes
それを心筋細胞に変える
turn it into nerve cells
それを神経細胞に変える
turn it into liver cells
肝細胞に変える
I just said one day we'll have a
いつかそうするだろうと言いました。
Taiwanese special heart chip
台湾特製ハートチップ
Taiwanese special liver chips
台湾特製レバーチップス
Taiwanese special neural chip
台湾製特殊ニューラルチップ
We can do drug screening
薬物スクリーニングを行うことができます
We can come and check for disease
病気の有無を調べに来てもらえます
Personalized medicine, of course
個別化医療はもちろん
That's what we're talking about
それが私たちが話していることです
future clinical trials
今後の臨床試験
No need to actually capture 100 patients
実際に 100 人の患者を捕まえる必要はない
Give him this medicine and try to see if there is any response
この薬を彼に与えて、反応があるかどうかを確認してください
We just have to test it on this wafer
このウェーハでテストするだけです
It is possible to obtain the most preliminary results
最も初期的な結果を得ることが可能
So this is called what we are talking about now
これが私たちが今話していることと呼ばれるものです
clinical trials on a chip
チップ上の臨床試験
or a clinical trial in a test tube
または試験管内での臨床試験
就Cinco Trial on a chip
チップ上のCincoトライアル
or Cincotrile in a tube
またはチューブ内のシンコトリル
that's what we're going to do
それが私たちがやろうとしていることです
this this this
これこれこれ
The reason for the project
project的理由
Then we took the traditional one, of course.
その後、もちろん伝統的な方法を採用しました。
This way of life in Shandong
山東省のこんな暮らし
Then we use the technology of Sentai virus
そこで戦隊ウイルスの技術を利用する
IPS cells can be achieved by drawing blood
IPS細胞は採血によって得られる
And in Taiwan we have six hospitals, partner hospitals
台湾には6つの病院と提携病院があります
North, middle, south and east
北、中、南、東
It is National Taiwan University Hospital Taipei Veterans General Hospital of Traditional Chinese Medicine
国立台湾大学病院 台北退役軍人総医院です
City University Hospital, Gao Medical University Hospital and Tzu Chi Hospital
市立大学病院、高医科大学病院、慈済病院
These are the patients we collect
これらは私たちが集めた患者たちです
There are also sources of clinician collaboration
臨床医の協力源もあります
Our Biomedical Institute at the Hospital of Traditional Chinese Medicine
漢方病院の生物医学研究所
At National Taiwan University Hospital, Taipei Veterans General Hospital, National Health and Rescue Hospital
国立台湾大学病院、台北退役軍人総合病院、国立衛生救護病院にて
and construction
そして建設
can do this kind of service
このようなサービスができます
Generate these IPS cells
これらの IPS セルを生成します
After it's done, it will be sent to the biomedical center of the hospital of traditional Chinese medicine.
検査が完了したら、中医病院の生物医学センターに送られます。
Let's do an analysis with the construction company
建設会社と一緒に分析してみましょう
confirm this is good
これが良いことを確認してください
is available and can be stored
利用可能で保管可能です
It is open to everyone to apply for and use
どなたでもお申込み・ご利用いただけます
Then it will be placed in the construction site for everyone to apply
その後、誰もが申請できるように建設現場に設置されます
This is our whole consoling guy
これが私たちのすべての慰めです
The main manpower and the main manpower of our biomedical institute
私たちの生物医学研究所の主要な人材と主要な人材
such a study
そのような研究
two months ago
2ヶ月前
Originally made an appointment with Xingai Amalaka
もともとシンガイ・アマラカと約束していた
Sanzhong uncooked rice
三中の生米
This is Mr. Toyota
豊田さんです
He used to be from Taiwan, he can
彼はもともと台湾出身でした。
Zhongcai who beat Wuting Pharmaceutical Factory
五亭製薬廠を破った中才
Later, after retiring, I returned to Japan for more than half
その後退職後、半分以上日本に帰国
has he been in taiwan long
彼は台湾に長くいますか
Long-distance relationship with Taiwan
台湾との遠距離恋愛
one of his favorite things to do
彼の好きなことの一つ
It's like helping Taiwan to develop relations with Japan
台湾と日本との関係発展を支援するようなものです。
so through his relationship
だから彼の関係を通して
I had an appointment to go with
一緒に行く約束をしました
Meeting of Kunia Malaka
クニア・マラカ氏との出会い
How to talk about this sea swan
このウミハクチョウについてどう話せばいいのか
because he does it
彼がやるから
Grandpa who did this
これをやったおじいちゃん
so i don't want to talk about the winner
だから勝者については話したくない
promised
約束した
But the day before, I was suddenly called to Tokyo
でも前日に急に東京に呼ばれたんです。
prime minister
首相
What does the Prime Minister of Japan want from him?
日本の首相は彼に何を望んでいますか？
So then they had Deputy Director
それで彼らには副所長がいた
come out with us and talk like this
私たちと一緒に出てきてこうやって話しましょう
They also want to be with us
彼らも私たちと一緒にいたいと思っています
Do it together with us
私たちと一緒にやってみませんか
this is what he said
これは彼が言ったことです
I don't know if I'm talking
話しているのか分かりません
He said that the genetics of the Japanese are very similar to those of the Taiwanese
日本人の遺伝子は台湾人と非常に似ていると彼は言った。
i don't know his
彼のことは知りません
where did he come from like this
彼はどこからこんなふうに来たのですか
But this kind of cooperation is always good
しかし、この種の協力は常に良いものです
I always feel that
いつもそう感じています
Taiwan happens to be in the center of the Asia Pacific
台湾はたまたまアジア太平洋の中心にあります
Taiwan also has the best in the world
台湾にも世界最高の選手がいる
at least one of the health care
少なくとも 1 つの医療
such a system
そのようなシステム
so we have very good
だから私たちはとても良いものを持っています
basic research person
基礎研究者
have good clinicians
良い臨床医がいる
So if we can build it into a
それで、それを構築できれば、
Asia-Pacific One Biomedicine
アジア太平洋地域のひとつの生物医学
biotechnology industry
バイオテクノロジー産業
such a central word
そんな中心的な言葉
i think we have a good chance
私たちには良いチャンスがあると思う
This will also be helpful for us
これは私たちにとっても役立ちます
This is also my cooperation with the dean and vice dean
これも学部長、副学部長との協力です
There are also seniors who are working in many courtyards
たくさんの中庭で働いている先輩もいます
Hope to be in the National Biotechnology Research Area
国立バイオテクノロジー研究領域への参加を希望する
We can be able to do Taiwan's more cutting-edge
台湾のもっと最先端のことができる
advanced such a creature
そのような進化した生き物
A development of the biotechnology industry
バイオテクノロジー産業の発展
In the end, of course we all have to thank us
もちろん最後にはみんなに感謝しなければなりません
cooperation partner
協力パートナー
At the Bank of China Hospital, at City University, National Taiwan University Hospital
中国銀行病院、市立大学、国立台湾大学病院にて
Construction Office, Ma Street, National Health Bureau Institute
国家健康局研究所、馬街の建設事務所
And our cooperation abroad
そして海外での協力
HARBORS、STANFORD、UC San Diego、UCSF
ハーバーズ、スタンフォード、UCサンディエゴ、UCSF
This is the former academician
元学者です
and this group in Karliski Sweden
そしてスウェーデンのカルリスキーのこのグループ
and Xiatu
そしてシアトゥ
In addition our funding is
さらに、私たちの資金は
Except for government agencies
政府機関以外の
We have some US pharmaceutical companies in the biotech industry
バイオテクノロジー業界には米国の製薬会社がいくつかあります
Bawasli European Army, Asbalanika, Takoda
バワスリ欧州軍、アスバラニカ、タコダ
And Taiwan's Malidi Army and Rebus Army
そして台湾のマリディ軍と判じ絵軍
Foreign pharmaceutical companies and Taiwanese design companies
外資系製薬会社と台湾のデザイン会社
Support and cooperation
支援と協力
that's our team
それが私たちのチームです
Current team at the firm
会社の現在のチーム
Finally I'll just take a minute
最後に少しだけ時間をいただきます
This is my doctor's teacher
これは私の医者の先生です
Dr. A.S. Eli Cruz
A.S.博士イーライ・クルーズ
he passed away last year
彼は昨年亡くなりました
he is one of mine
彼は私の一人です
A role model for my life
私の人生のロールモデル
i just mentioned
先ほど言いました
he is in the hub
彼は港にいる
Completed by Harper School of Medicine
ハーパー医科大学修了
After getting his medical degree
医師の学位を取得した後
research training
研究研修
thirty years in seattle
シアトル在住30年
build the entire surgical
外科手術全体を構築する
The system of this study looks like this
今回の研究のシステムはこんな感じです
he's always been great to me
彼はいつも私に素晴らしかったです
I've always said he's the best teacher in the world
私はいつも彼が世界で最高の教師だと言いました
the best person
最高の人
Anyway, among the tens of thousands of people in Huada
とにかく、花田にいる何万人もの人々の間で
If
もしも
If everyone says only one person is good
みんなが一人だけいいって言うなら
everyone else is bad
他の人はみんな悪い
that good man is him
あのいい人は彼です
that's the kind of person
それはそういう人です
so
それで
He has always encouraged me positively
彼はいつも私を前向きに励ましてくれました
So I don't have this teacher's encouragement
だから私にはこの先生の励ましはありません
I can go on. I have a very important one this time.
続けます。今回は非常に重要な話があります。
But now he passed away last year like this
でも彼は去年こうして亡くなってしまいました
that's sad too
それも悲しい
Mr. Li Xudong, former deputy director of our firm
弊社元副所長 李 徐東氏
He also passed away last week
彼も先週亡くなりました
Then he was the person who influenced me the most when I returned to Taiwan
そして台湾に戻った私に最も影響を与えてくれたのが彼でした。
because this can't go on
これは続けられないから
I can't go on, I can't go on
続けられない、続けられない
anyway he has always given us a very positive kind of power like this
とにかく彼はいつも私たちにこのようなとてもポジティブな力を与えてくれました
Because when I was growing up
だって私が成長した頃
peace in the business
ビジネスにおける平和
Come here two days a week
週に2日ここに来てください
So the incident is here for over six years
つまりこの事件は6年以上続いている
And the time he is not in the event room is actually him
そして、彼がイベントルームにいない時間は、実際には彼です
Because he still comes every day after retirement
退職後も毎日来てくれるから
The student, he discussed with the student
学生、彼は学生と話し合いました
Taking care of the students, teachers, mothers, and the owners all provide delicious food for the students
生徒の面倒を見て、先生もお母さんもオーナーもみんなで生徒たちに美味しいご飯を提供してくれる
That's why the students all looked for him instead of me.
そこで生徒たちは皆、私の代わりに彼を探しました。
Because you find me, you say this to me
あなたが私を見つけたから、あなたは私にこれを言います
So then I said, teacher, please be a bit more white.
そこで私は、「先生、もう少し白くしてください」と言いました。
I'm half black and you want to be half black
私は半分黒人ですが、あなたは半分黒人になりたいのです
Otherwise, students won't be serious about this
そうでないと生徒たちは真剣に考えないでしょう
He wrote very good calligraphy
彼はとても上手な書道を書きました
he passed away last week like this
彼は先週こうして亡くなりました
I think
私が思うに
I'll stop here
ここでやめておきます
that has a little time
それは少し時間があります
still some time
まだしばらく
We can all come and continue the discussion like this
みんなで集まってこうやって議論を続けてもいいよ
Excuse me
すみません
Lali Lala talked a lot
ラリララはたくさん話しました
Hope it helps
それが役に立てば幸い
Let's work hard together
一緒に頑張りましょう
Thanks
ありがとう
Thank you for the wonderful speech after the social
懇親会後の素晴らしいスピーチありがとうございました
yes see these people
はい、この人たちを見てください
go one by one
一つ一つ行きます
It's also very sad
それはとても悲しいことでもある
Xu Dong and I are also very popular
Xu Dongと私もとても人気があります
i didn't know he passed away
彼が亡くなったことを知りませんでした
But why do you write the number 24 here?
しかし、なぜここに24という数字を書くのでしょうか？
The 24th is today
24日は今日です
today is the 23rd
今日は23日です
Today is the world wrong
今日の世界は間違っています
it was last saturday
先週の土曜日でした
last saturday
この間の土曜日
OK
OK
good
良い
I think there should be many
たくさんあってもいいと思うよ
I want to ask our teacher thank you
先生にお願いしたいのですが、ありがとうございます
Come
来て
Thank you teacher for your wonderful speech
先生、素晴らしいスピーチをありがとうございました
That
それか
What I'm slightly curious about is that
ちょっと気になるのは、
Great efforts have been made in
多大な努力が払われてきた
To allow cells to associate with therapeutic substances
細胞が治療物質と会合できるようにするため
Where
どこ
Then I have heard that there seems to be some methods, such as
そうすると、次のような方法があるらしいと聞いたことがあります。
where to stick it like a thing
物のようにどこに貼り付けるか
Didn't notice you didn't use this method
この方法を使っていないことに気づきませんでした
I even saw that at the back of your speech you said
あなたのスピーチの最後であなたがこう言ったのも見ました
Make a scheming patch that works
機能する計画パッチを作成する
I don't know if I have thought about it
考えたことがあるかどうかはわかりませんが、
That is to say, between the scheming patch and the necrotic scheming
つまり、陰謀パッチと壊死陰謀の間
Maybe put that several different
たぶん、いくつかの異なるものを置く
You can take this material to regenerate it
この素材を取り出して再生することができます
Is it possible to do the same
同じことは可能ですか
Or why you don't do it thank you
それともなぜそうしないのですか、ありがとう
Because you want the cells of your scheming patch to be the same as the original scheming
スキームパッチのセルを元のスキームと同じにする必要があるため
The cells of the heart can integrate together
心臓の細胞は統合できる
So it's best to just
したがって、それが最善です
close together
近くに
If there is a thing between you
あなたとの間に何かあるなら
it might not work
うまくいかないかもしれない
lock together jump together
ロックロック一緒にジャンプ
the answer is as simple as that
答えはとても簡単です
Thanks
ありがとう
Or about one in every thousand people in advanced countries will die suddenly
あるいは先進国では1000人に1人くらいが突然亡くなるだろう
You also mentioned the research in this area of ​​Xinji Kesi many times
Xinji Kesiのこの分野の研究についても何度も言及しましたね
I don't know if the best
最高かどうかはわかりません
It's the teacher, you have solved all the problems of Xinji Kesi
それは先生です、あなたはXinji Kesiの問題をすべて解決しました
Then the rate of one in a thousand sudden deaths
すると突然死は1000人に1人の割合で
How much do you think can be solved
どれくらい解決できると思いますか
ok thanks this is an important question
わかりました、ありがとう、これは重要な質問です
We have a plan with Dr. Chen Shi'an from Taipei Veterans General
台北退役軍人総局の陳世安博士と計画を立てています。
Because Dr. Chen Shi'an works as a psychological minister all over the world.
なぜなら、チェン・シーアン博士は世界中で心理牧師として働いているからです。
I think being the leader is very important for a group
リーダーになることはグループにとってとても重要なことだと思う
Then all we have to do is say
それなら私たちがしなければならないのはこう言うことだけです
For those patients who already know he already has a psych minister
彼にすでに精神大臣がいることを知っている患者たちへ
but don't know why
でもなぜだかわからない
Similarly, we can't take all these patients to cut their hearts and cut them into pieces for examination.
同様に、これらの患者全員を検査のために心臓を切り取ったり、細かく切り刻んだりすることはできません。
So we hope to draw blood from these patients
したがって、私たちはこれらの患者から採血したいと考えています
Turn it into IPS cells and turn it into psycho cells
IPS細胞に変えてサイコ細胞に変える
come and see him
彼に会いに来てください
What's wrong with these new cells
これらの新しい細胞の何が問題なのか
The advantage of this is that
この利点は、
if you want to cut a sick heart
病んだ心を断ち切りたいなら
At most, the patient will ask you to cut a small piece for research.
せいぜい、患者が研究のために小さな断片を切り取ってほしいと頼む程度です。
A small piece with few cells
細胞数が少ない小さな断片
only do it once
一度だけやってください
at most once
多くても一度
I will never let you do it the second time
二度目は絶対に許さない
But if we put his two thin blood
でももし彼の2つの薄い血を入れたら
Turn into IPS into new cells
IPSを新しい細胞に変える
In theory we can get infinite
理論的には無限に取得できます
New Cells with Unlimited Craftsmanship
無限の職人技による新しいセル
can do a lot of research
たくさんの研究ができる
with drug screening
薬物検査付き
This is also another
これもまた別の
The Approach to Personalized Medicine
個別化医療へのアプローチ
In other words, why the patient has been
言い換えれば、患者がなぜそうなったのかというと、
Anticardiac drugs have been doing poorly
抗心臓薬の効果が芳しくない
Sometimes it's even hard to control
時にはコントロールするのが難しいことさえあります
what is the reason
理由は何ですか
You can't always take his heart
いつも彼の心を奪えるわけではない
make slices for inspection
検査用にスライスを作成する
Even do the electrophysiology of the heart like this
心臓の電気生理学もこんな感じでやります
Those are actually pretty dangerous
それらは実際にはかなり危険です
But we can put his
しかし、私たちは彼のことを置くことができます
Blood-drawn IPS turns into new cells
血液から採取されたIPSは新しい細胞に変わります
We can do drug screening
薬物スクリーニングを行うことができます
Mechanism of making drugs
薬ができる仕組み
Finally you can talk to him
ついに彼と話せます
It turned out to be like this
このようになりました
This drug is actually the best choice for you
この薬は実はあなたにとって最良の選択です
instead of asking the patient to
患者に求めるのではなく、
what are we
私たちは何ですか
be a white mouse
白いネズミになる
In fact, many patients sometimes act as guinea pigs
実際、多くの患者がモルモットとして行動することがあります。
The doctor is also working as a guinea pig
医者もモルモットとして働いています
But the doctor loves the patient more and is the weaker side
でも医者は患者のことをもっと愛しているし、弱い側でもある。
So if we use these techniques
したがって、これらのテクニックを使用すると、
Let the patient know earlier
患者さんには早めに知らせてください
In fact, what kind of drug choice is best for you
実際、どのような薬を選択するのがあなたにとって最適ですか
This will be of great help to patients
これは患者さんにとって非常に助かります
Emergy comes
緊急事態が到来
ask the teacher
先生に尋ねる
The experiment you just talked about
あなたが今話した実験
I need people and money
人も金も必要だ
but spend so much time
しかし、とても多くの時間を費やして
Is it faster if you give more money and more people
より多くのお金とより多くの人を提供した方が早いですか？
Turned ten years into one month
10年を1ヶ月にしました
will have such an effect
このような効果があるでしょう
If you have a big team
大きなチームがある場合
and many
そして多くの
Is this progress so fast?
この進歩はそんなに速いですか？
And you have made a lot of achievements
そして、あなたは多くの成果を上げてきました
I guess the question is a bit complicated
質問は少し複雑だと思います
we can't say
私たちは言えません
Everyone don't do it, I just do it
みんながやるのではなく、私がやるだけです
Because there are quite a lot of complicated factors
かなり複雑な要素があるので
but i am
でも私はそうよ
I don't know what the vice-president or the secretary-general think
副大統領や事務総長がどう思っているかは分からない
because i have a friend
私には友達がいるから
He is the leader of the Singapore relationship package like this
彼はこのようなシンガポール関係パッケージのリーダーです
He is actually involved in many government policies
彼は実際に多くの政府政策に関与している
Policy formulation and budget allocation
政策策定と予算配分
I envy him
彼が羨ましいです
Because every year he meets me, he tells me
なぜなら彼は私に会うたびにこう言うからです。
How much more has our tech budget grown
技術予算はさらにどれくらい増えたのか
That's the latest I was last time
前回はそれが最新でした
The meeting organized by NOVATIS at the Hospital of Traditional Chinese Medicine
NOVATIS主催による中医薬病院でのミーティングの様子
He'll tell me about his tech budget
彼は技術予算について教えてくれるでしょう
I calculated that we were probably
私たちはおそらくそうだろうと計算しました
Are we about 100 billion a year?
年間1000億くらいでしょうか？
almost
ほとんど
their annual tech budget
年間技術予算
Now it has grown to about 300 billion Taiwan dollars a year
今では年間約3,000億台湾ドルにまで成長しています
ever less than us
私たちよりもずっと下です
The population of Singapore is only slightly more than a quarter of ours
シンガポールの人口は私たちの人口の4分の1をわずかに上回るだけです
So they're just over a quarter of our population
つまり、彼らは私たちの人口の4分の1強を占めています
His tech budget is three times ours a year
彼の技術予算は年間で私たちの予算の 3 倍です
So it turns into saying
だからそれはこう言うことになる
What is the average technology budget for each person?
一人当たりの平均テクノロジー予算はいくらですか?
12 times
12倍
i remember i want to go abroad
海外に行きたいのを覚えています
1990 when going out
1990年 外出時
I was already an old student
私はすでに古い学生でした
What scared me that year was
その年私が怖かったのは
In 1999, Singapore decided to invest in the biotechnology industry
1999 年、シンガポールはバイオテクノロジー産業への投資を決定しました。
So they started to spend 30 billion Taiwan dollars a year, and then they spent it like this
それで彼らは年間300億台湾ドルを使い始め、その後このように使いました
Later, it has been growing until now it is 300 billion
その後増え続けて今では3000億です
So I have to be honest and say that our research on dry bags is actually a lot behind Singapore.
したがって、正直に言うと、私たちのドライバッグは研究の点でシンガポールにはるかに遅れをとっています。
They can occupy a group overnight in the world and we can't
彼らは世界中で一夜にしてグループを占領することができますが、私たちはそれができません
so i think we might have to try harder
だからもっと頑張らなければいけないかもしれないと思う
Of course, if the government is in financial difficulties, everyone knows that under the circumstances of financial difficulties
もちろん、政府が財政難に陥っているなら、財政難の状況下では誰もがそれを知っています。
We may not be able to do everything, we have to pick some priorities to do
すべてを行うことはできないかもしれませんが、やるべき優先順位をいくつか選択する必要があります
Maybe it's just like what the director of the upgrader district said, what we have to do
おそらくそれはアップグレード地区のディレクターが言ったことと同じです、私たちがしなければならないこと
Can't do everything but we have to do it best
すべてを行うことはできませんが、最善を尽くす必要があります
Recently, with the representatives of the Netherlands in Taiwan, they are hoping to establish cooperation
最近、台湾のオランダ代表と協力関係を確立したいと考えています。
Even encouraged us to go to the Netherlands to cooperate with us like this
このように私たちに協力するためにオランダに行くよう勧めてくれました。
They say that even the technology of the world like the Netherlands
オランダのような世界の技術でも
Here in the powerhouse of biotechnology
ここバイオテクノロジーの本拠地
They also only choose a few fields to work hard to do this
彼らはまた、これを行うために熱心に取り組む分野をいくつか選択するだけです
will be competitive
競争力があるだろう
I don't know if this will help us
これが私たちの役に立つかどうかわかりません
If we say that this is a
これがだと言うと、
We are worth investing in, worth doing
私たちは投資する価値があり、実行する価値があります
In fact, there are some fields in Taiwan that are quite competitive.
実際、台湾には非常に競争が激しい分野がいくつかあります。
is quite competitive
かなり競争力がある
It will help if we do this
こうすれば助かるよ
It’s like we established the console of the IPA club
IPAクラブのコンソールを設立したようなものです
In fact, it was proposed more than three years ago.
実はこれは3年以上前に提案されていたんです。
but many people disagree
しかし、多くの人は反対します
Reasons for disagreement will feel like saying
意見の相違の理由はこう言いたくなるでしょう
Before doing stem cells in Taiwan, there were really few
台湾で幹細胞を行う前は、幹細胞は本当にほとんどありませんでした。
It will be troublesome to talk about this
これについて話すのは面倒だろう
If we use some of the resources to do this
これを行うためにリソースの一部を使用すると、
then the others will decrease
そうすれば他も減るだろう
but then again
でもまたまた
If we feel that this is the right thing to do
私たちがこれを行うべきだと感じた場合
we will do it
私たちがやります
It's not about taking Nobio. It's already taken.
のびおを奪うんじゃなくて、もう奪われたんだよ。
It is not for the cooperation of Nature Science
Nature Scienceの協力によるものではありません
neither
ない
It's actually for our own national health
実は私たち自身の国民の健康のため
For our research projects
私たちの研究プロジェクトのために
For our basic strength
私たちの基礎力のために
So even if you don't want to take Nature Science
したがって、たとえNature Scienceを受講したくないとしても、
I don't want to talk about it even if you don't want to post NATURE Science
NATURE Scienceを投稿したくないとしても、それについては話したくない
You still have to do it and try to do it well
あなたはまだそれをしなければなりません、そしてそれをうまくやるように努めなければなりません
So we actually have the same scale
つまり、実際には同じスケールになります
The money we use is less than one tenth of that of foreign countries
私たちが使うお金は外国の10分の1以下です
But I think it's time to do it
でも、それをする時期が来たと思う
So last year was our first project of the whole year
去年は今年最初のプロジェクトでした
Our laboratory has posted 3 million such
私たちの研究室ではそのようなものを300万件投稿しています
Mourn this to the vice president
副大統領にこれを悼んでください
I hope this year will not be like this, we will lose another 3 million like this
今年はこうならないことを祈ります、このまままた300万人を失うことになるでしょう
do it when it's time to do it
やる時が来たらやる
i always feel like saying
いつも言いたくなる
Everyone sitting here thank you so much
ここに座っている皆さん、本当にありがとう
every dime
一銭ごとに
it's all taxpayer money
それはすべて国民の税金です
including my own tax money
自分の税金も含めて
we can't run away for a dime
私たちは一銭のためにも逃げることはできません
So it's really the responsibility to do it well
ですから、それをうまくやるのが本当に責任です
Can't be wasted
無駄にはできない
If I'm a student again, listen up
また学生になったら聞いてください
I've said it many times
何度も言いました
Our scientific research money is the taxpayer's money
私たちの科学研究費は国民の税金です
we can also waste
無駄にすることもできます
I want to ask that teacher
あの先生に聞きたい
You said two CCs of blood were drawn for the IPS
IPSのために2CCの採血が行われたと言いました
Is it specific to your patients or in general
それはあなたの患者に特有のものですか、それとも一般的なものですか
People with average IQ can
平均的な IQ を持つ人は、
It will be all right
大丈夫ですよ
are all
全てです
how to express
どのように表現するか
if i say yes
私が「はい」と言えば
then go
それから行きます
Even if you are not a patient
患者でなくても
Can IQ people do it too?
IQの人でもできるでしょうか？
I have to apologize to you for this
このことについてあなたに謝らなければなりません
because it takes a long time
長い時間がかかるので
spend a lot of money
たくさんのお金を費やします
if you are abroad
海外にいる場合
you say
あなたは言う
i wish to know
知りたいです
I'm going to make my own IPSELS
自分だけのIPSELSを作ってみる
you need to spend at least thirty thousand dollars
あなたは少なくとも3万ドルを費やす必要があります
to be able to make your appearance
自分の姿を見せることができるように
That is to say, I am willing to shed two nights of blood
つまり、私は二晩血を流す覚悟があるということだ
I have to pay
支払わなければなりません
That is to say, if you want to make
つまり、作りたい場合は、
Your own cells that you can use in the future
将来使える自分の細胞
right
右
It's like this in foreign countries
外国ではこんな感じ
what we do now
私達が現在行っていること
We really have to be selective
本当に選択的でなければなりません
with object
オブジェクト付き
have a specific object
特定のオブジェクトを持っている
yes
はい
So if say
それで言うなら
you already know
あなたが既に知っている
when your own genotype
あなた自身の遺伝子型が
then we can discuss
それなら話し合えるよ
Thanks
ありがとう
then you might be
そうすればあなたもそうなるかもしれません
one of our rare
私たちの珍しいものの一つ
then we'll do it for you for free
それなら無料でやります
But you have to Promise
でも約束しなければならない
same idea
同じ考え
that is
あれは
We donate with all of these
これらすべてを寄付させていただきます
including patients
患者さんも含めて
Including the doctor, we help him do it for free
医師も含めて私たちは無料で彼のお手伝いをします
it's government money
それは政府のお金です
He wants to promise one thing
彼は一つ約束したいことがある
after making it
作った後
You need to be able to expose technology
テクノロジーを公開できる必要がある
for everyone to use
誰もが使えるように
Of course this patient donor profile
もちろん、この患者ドナープロフィール
we can't make it public
それを公開することはできません
This IRB has that
この治験審査委員会にはそれがあります
That must be protected by the Personal Data Law
それは個人情報法で保護される必要があります
but you must agree to say
しかし、あなたは言うことに同意しなければなりません
we do a good job for you
私たちはあなたのために良い仕事をします
And guarantee the best quality
最高の品質を保証します
but you have to donate
でも寄付しなければなりません
available for everyone to use
誰でも利用できる
that makes sense
それは理にかなっている
i mean
つまり
is your object enough
あなたの目的は十分ですか
we are still growing
私たちはまだ成長しています
yes
はい
We will have a more familiar problem
もっと身近な問題が出てきます
I've been doing this report for a while now.
久しぶりにこのレポートを書きました。
Because now everyone cares about the biotech industry
なぜなら今では誰もがバイオテクノロジー産業に関心を持っているからです
Newspapers for the past two days
過去 2 日間の新聞
you can also see
あなたも見ることができます
Our euro has always been long
私たちのユーロは常に長かった
on board
機内で
this stem cell
この幹細胞
What are the uses that are actually in use now?
実際に現在はどのような用途に使われているのでしょうか？
Because you can also see that there are many companies
たくさんの会社があることもわかりますので
As you said just now, the two details
今おっしゃったように、この 2 つの詳細は
There are also people who use chicken blood to save it again, etc.
鶏の血を使って再度保存する人もいます。
A lot of business activities are going on
多くの事業活動が行われています
these things
これらの事
Is it all useful or is it
それはすべて役に立ちますか、それとも
I'm not saying which stock I'm going to invest in
どの銘柄に投資するかは言いません
But I really don't know
でも本当に分からない
these stem cells
これらの幹細胞
current
現在
Let me give you an example of what can be used in practice
実際に使える例をご紹介します
A few years ago because my teeth had to be treated
数年前に歯の治療が必要になったので
this bone is not good
この骨は良くない
they just
彼らはただ
I just installed this bone powder, wait a minute, I heard that there are also stem cells in it
この骨粉をインストールしたところです。ちょっと待ってください。幹細胞も入っていると聞きました。
Then he promotes this
それから彼はこれを宣伝します
skeletal
骨格的な
the real body of my skeleton
私の骸骨の本当の体
so that is
それはそうです
looks feasible
実現可能に見える
and already confident
そしてすでに自信を持って
So stem cells are now in
つまり、幹細胞は現在、
What are the things that are generally used
一般的に使われているものは何ですか
Chairman, this is a big problem
議長、これは大きな問題です
different stem cells
さまざまな幹細胞
Different stem cells have different uses
幹細胞が異なれば用途も異なります
So far
ここのところ
was in Japan
在日本被
There are three licensed products that are ready for commercialization
商品化の準備が整っているライセンス製品は 3 つあります
The first one is whether you want to guess
1つ目は、推測したいかどうかです
what was the first stem cell product
最初の幹細胞製品は何でしたか
or products of regenerative medicine
または再生医療製品
Products for regenerative medicine including stem cell tissue engineering
幹細胞組織工学を含む再生医療向け製品
The first product is
最初の製品は
Probably the skin, the skin is the easiest
たぶん皮です、皮が一番簡単です
So when we get mad, there are people in Japan who help
だから私たちが怒ったとき、日本には助けてくれる人がいる
So their first product was
そこで彼らの最初の製品は
In the case of a burn patient
火傷患者の場合
he takes a small piece of skin
彼は小さな皮膚片を取り出します
Can give you the whole tablet within a week
1週間以内にタブレット全体をお届けします
my skin looks like this
私の肌はこんな感じです
The second product is cartilage
2番目の製品は軟骨です
So using arthroscopic very small wounds
そこで、関節鏡視下の非常に小さな傷を使用して、
Take a small piece of cartilage and raise it a lot
軟骨の小さな部分を取り出して大きく持ち上げます
It's time to fix it
それを直す時が来た
a month's time
一個月的時間
to repair your own cells.
自分自身の細胞を修復するために。
third heart
第三の心臓
The heart is the same is to take that
それを受け止めることは心も同じだ
top stem cells
トップ幹細胞
Muses Kamas stem cells
ミューズ カマス幹細胞
it's the same as laying it on
敷いているのと同じです
A membrane called Ph sensitive
Ph感受性と呼ばれる膜
This is their Japanese unique technology
これが日本独自の技術です
That is to say, the cells
つまり、細胞は、
after planting on that membrane
その膜に植えた後
temperature change
温度変化
The film will roll up
フィルムが巻き上がってしまいます
You don't need to knock it down
倒す必要はないよ
it will survive better
そのほうがよく生き残れるだろう
So this film can be attached to
このフィルムは次のようなものに取り付けることができます。
damaged surface of the myocardium
心筋の損傷した表面
It's the Sawar from Osaka University
大阪大学のサワルです。
what they are doing
彼らは何をやってるの
it was them a month ago
1ヶ月前は彼らだった
Just been approved
承認されたばかりです
Japan Postsei approved
日本後生生approved
The third product looks like this
3つ目の商品はこんな感じ
right
右
Didn't you use it when you pressed it?
押したときに使わなかったのですか？
Um
えーっと
do you really have stem cells or fake
本当に幹細胞を持っていますか、それとも偽物ですか
actually stem cells
実は幹細胞
a lot
多くの
a lot of
たくさんの
stick to stem cells a lot
幹細胞にたくさんくっつく
what you just said
あなたが今言ったこと
Insistence on stem cells does exist
幹細胞に対するこだわりは存在します
And because sticking to stem cells
そして、幹細胞にこだわっているため、
Its purpose is to grow bones
その目的は骨を成長させることです
long cartilage
長軟骨
So it's actually make sense
それは実際には理にかなっています
This is done in many places abroad
海外では多くの場所で行われています
just say a lot of stuff like this
このようなことをたくさん言ってください
it
それ
to Japan
以日本
Japan because of cell therapy
細胞治療のおかげで日本
Go to the forefront and the fastest
一番早く行く
In Japan
日本で
it's up to now really its epigenetic province
それは今のところ本当にエピジェネティックな領域です
Heke's company
ヘケの会社
Cellular products that can be made
作れる細胞製品
just these three
この3つだけ
Everything else is done in the hospital
それ以外はすべて病院内で行われます
it's easy in japan
日本では簡単です
we just talked
私たちはちょうど話したばかりです
Our cell therapy application for three years
3年間にわたる当社の細胞療法アプリケーション
still can't do it
まだ出来ない
In Japan as long as it is
日本にいる限り
Hospital IRB Consent
病院の治験審査委員会の同意
it can directly do
それは直接行うことができます
No need to go through your epigenetic province
エピジェネティックな領域を通過する必要はありません
this cartilage to
この軟骨を
this joint this
このジョイントはこれ
Nearly the whole doctor is not there
医師はほぼ全員不在です
Do something like this?
こんなことしてみませんか？
That
それか
Seems to be doing quite well
かなりうまくいっているようだ
doing clinical trials
臨床試験を行っている
right
右
still doing clinical trials
まだ臨床試験を行っている
OK
OK
I don't know if there are any other problems
他に問題があるかどうかはわかりません
no matter the heart
心とは関係なく
or stem cells
または幹細胞
very important now
今とても重要な
I'm sorry, I'll just ask one more question
すみません、もう一つだけ質問させていただきます
The teacher just mentioned stem cells and also mentioned that different countries have different degrees of loosening research
先生は先ほど幹細胞について言及し、国によって緩みの研究の度合いが異なることにも言及しました。
Now in Taiwan, I seem to have heard that if you are not very familiar with it, you can’t use Petai stem cells.
今台湾では、ペタイ幹細胞はよく知らないと使えない、と聞いたことがあります。
Then we need to untie this side so that researchers can dispute the use of
次に、研究者がその使用に異議を唱えられるように、この側面を解きほぐす必要があります。
Stem cells, do you think this is appropriate or something?
幹細胞、これは適切だと思いますか？
Petai stem cells cannot be used in advanced countries
ペタイ幹細胞は先進国では使えない
human
人的
Except for very few clinical careers
ごく一部の臨床キャリアを除いて
All
全て
No country has approved
どの国も承認していない
Petai Stem Cells Turned into a Product
Petai幹細胞が製品化
for cell therapy
細胞治療用
Currently there is no
現在はありません
Because Petai Stem Cells
ペタイ幹細胞だから
to not quite
完全ではない
Ethical considerations
倫理的配慮
Because Petai Stem Cells
ペタイ幹細胞だから
he has great potential
彼は素晴らしいポテンシャルを持っている
As I just said, he can become more than 200 kinds of physiological cells
先ほども言いましたが、彼は200種類以上の生理細胞になれるのです。
very capable
能力非常強
but you want only one of them
でも、そのうちの 1 つだけが必要です
You injected embryonic stem cells into the heart today
あなたは今日、心臓に胚性幹細胞を注入しました
Although it may grow cardiomyocytes
心筋細胞が増殖する可能性はありますが、
but it will grow other
しかし、それは他のものに成長します
in trouble
トラブルにあっている
So we know very little about embryonic stem cells
そのため、胚性幹細胞についてはほとんどわかっていません。
So it's better to say
だから言ったほうがいいよ
We call embryonic stem cells or IPSEL
私たちは胚性幹細胞または IPSEL と呼んでいます。
turn it into various cells
さまざまな細胞に変える
for drug screening, toxicology testing
薬物スクリーニング、毒性試験用
Discussion of genes, even personalized medicine
遺伝子、さらには個別化医療についての議論
this is no problem
これは問題ありません
But if you want to turn these into a product
しかし、これらを製品にしたい場合は、
it's more difficult
それはもっと難しいです
But there are many companies
でも会社はたくさんあるよ
What you are doing now is just like what the vice president said just now
あなたが今やっていることは、今副大統領が言ったことと同じです。
That is, they store cells
つまり細胞を蓄えているのです
After storage, it can be made into various treatments in the future
保管後、将来的にさまざまな加工が可能
For example, our
たとえば、私たちの
this should be able to speak
これは話せるはずだ
All papers have been published
すべての論文が出版されました
sorry i go back
ごめんなさい、戻ります
For example, that Selgen
たとえばあのセルゲン
This is one of the largest pharmaceutical companies in the United States
これは米国最大の製薬会社の 1 つです
Their strategy is the same as some companies
彼らの戦略は一部の企業と同じです
that is to say they are
つまり彼らはそうです
Fascinity in GMP
GMPの魅力
under the laboratory that meets the specifications of that drug
その医薬品の仕様を満たす研究室の下で
just make it tube by tube
チューブごとに作るだけです
various stem cells
さまざまな幹細胞
Then take this tube of stem cells as
次に、この幹細胞のチューブを次のように取ります
Think of it like stem cells are also drugs
幹細胞も薬であると考えてください
So when it uses this stem cell as a drug
この幹細胞を薬として利用すると
Do clinical trials of clinical treatments for different diseases
さまざまな病気の臨床治療のための臨床試験を実施する
if it works
それがうまくいけば
In the future it will be approved by the US ADL
将来的には米国のADLによって承認される予定です
it can sell the drug
それは薬を売ることができる
for example
例えば
Of course, these are mainly diseases that cannot be treated at present.
もちろん、これらは現在治療できない病気が主です。
rare disease
稀な病気
mainly
主に
then if it works
それがうまくいけば
Then it can sell you a tube of cells in the future
そうすれば将来的には細胞のチューブを販売できるようになる
as medicine
薬として
So this pattern is more
したがって、このパターンはさらに
Most of them are like this now
今はほとんどがこんな感じです
just say
言うだけ
approved but still very limited
承認されましたが、まだ非常に限定的です
Are there any other questions?
他にご質問はありますか?
Our heart beats several times in a lifetime
私たちの心臓は一生に数回鼓動します
almost
ほとんど
I don't know how to count
数え方がわかりません
But our new exhibit has about 10 billion new machine cells
しかし、私たちの新しい展示品には約 100 億個の新しいマシンセルがあります
Did you have it just now please come please
今持ってましたか、来てください
I want to ask the teacher
先生に聞きたいのですが
That is to say, various cells differentiated from ESC and IPS
つまり、ESCやIPSから分化した様々な細胞
There seems to be some differences
多少の違いはあるようですが
don't know say such a difference
そんな違いが言えるか分からない
where is the difference
違いはどこにありますか
Cells differentiated from true IPS
真のIPSから分化した細胞
It can really be used for clinical application
本当に臨床応用できる
ok thanks for your question
わかりました、ご質問ありがとうございます
That is, wearing stem cells
つまり、幹細胞を身につけるということです
Derived new machine cells or nerve cells
派生した新しい機械細胞または神経細胞
Turn blood into IPS
血液をIPSに変える
Derived new machine cells and nerve cells
派生した新しい機械細胞と神経細胞
what's the difference
違いは何ですか
cannot replace
交換できません
Everyone's results are different
結果は人それぞれ違います
so there's no judging yet
だからまだ結論は出ていない
The simplest answer is this
最も単純な答えはこれです
No matter what, back to the origin is still the same
何があっても原点回帰は変わらない
That is to say
つまり
the purpose of that part
その部分の目的
We hope to be personalized medicine
個別化医療を目指します
You can imagine that we are doing about two hundred
私たちが約 200 件の作業を行っていると想像していただけますか
about two hundred
約二百
We all look different
私たちは皆違って見えます
so you can imagine
想像できるように
Each of us has a different heart
私たちはそれぞれ違う心を持っています
Each of us is genetically different
私たちはそれぞれ遺伝子的に異なります
so it's hard for you to say
だからあなたが言うのは難しい
You use one cell to have an effect on everyone
1 つのセルを使用して全員に影響を与える
even if you are a
たとえあなたが
have been clinically tested
臨床試験を受けています
I have been taking the medicine for twenty years
私はその薬を20年間服用しています
Everyone's reaction may still be different
みんなの反応はまだ異なるかもしれない
That creature is actually very complicated
あの生き物は実はとても複雑だ
I studied a medical engineering myself
私自身も医用工学を学びました
Doctor of Medicine
医学博士
He also worked as a postdoctoral fellow at MIT for several years
彼はMITで数年間ポスドク研究員としても働いた
deep feeling
深い感情
In fact, there is a big difference between biology and engineering.
実際、生物学と工学の間には大きな違いがあります。
Biology is far more complex than engineering
生物学は工学よりもはるかに複雑です
for example
例えば
For example, I used to be in Seattle
たとえば、私は以前シアトルにいました。
Everyone knows Boeing
ボーイングは誰もが知っています
He was flying in Seattle
彼はシアトルに飛んだ
That Boeing 747
那一台波音747
He has 30,000 parts
彼は30,000の部品を持っています
We probably have about 30,000 genes in that person
その人の遺伝子はおそらく約 30,000 個あります
That's it
それでおしまい
Those 30,000 Boeing 747 parts
ボーイング 747 の 30,000 個の部品
if everything is complete
すべてが完了していれば
experienced engineer
経験豊富なエンジニア
There are engineers and blueprints
エンジニアも設計図もある
spell it out
それを綴る
Come on, maybe you can drive and fly
さあ、車で飛んでいけるかもしれない
But 30,000 genes
でも遺伝子は3万個
Makes 30,000 proteins
30,000個のタンパク質を作る
In the past, one gene and one protein
かつては、1 つの遺伝子と 1 つのタンパク質
but it's not that simple
しかしそれはそれほど単純ではありません
Sometimes several genes and one protein
場合によっては複数の遺伝子と 1 つのタンパク質
Sometimes one gene and several proteins
場合によっては 1 つの遺伝子と複数のタンパク質
leave it alone
ほっといて
Thirty thousand genes count as three eggs
3万個の遺伝子は卵3個と数えられる
Thirty thousand proteins
3万個のタンパク質
as if we put
まるで私たちが置くかのように
Thirty thousand people locked in one room
3万人が1つの部屋に閉じ込められる
someone is sleeping
誰かが寝ています
someone is eating
誰かが食べています
someone is chatting
誰かがチャットしています
someone is playing
誰かが遊んでいます
Everyone reacts differently
人それぞれ反応が異なります
it produces these
それはこれらを生み出します
All combinations of pairings
ペアリングのすべての組み合わせ
Absolutely more than 30,000 parts
パーツ数はなんと30,000点以上
lie there without moving
動かずにそこに横たわってください
in terms of complexity
複雑さの点で
so this is a creature
だからこれは生き物だ
It's very different from an engineer
エンジニアとは大きく違う
Even if we have put
入れたとしても
Human Genome Project
ヒトゲノムプロジェクト
Complete the decoding of human genes
人間の遺伝子の解読を完了する
you have to study it
それを勉強しなければなりません
don't say in a hundred years
百年後とは言わないでください
maybe in a thousand years
おそらく千年以内に
we still only know
私たちはまだそれしか知りません
very small portion
ごく一部
Of course what you do now must be much better
もちろん、あなたが今やっていることはもっと良くなるはずです。
you ask me now
あなたは今私に尋ねます
These cells derived from ESL
ESL由来のこれらの細胞
How big is the difference
どれくらい違いますか
I think this is still case by case
これはまだケースバイケースだと思います
It is more important to return to their respective
それぞれの立場に戻ることがより重要です
come please
来てください
thank you teacher
ありがとう、先生
Just now you mentioned that there are new
先ほど、新しいものがあるとおっしゃいましたが、
new long-term disease
長期にわたる新たな病気
We are in prime time for four days
4日間はゴールデンタイムです
can do a reminder
リマインダーを行うことができます
a practical problem
現実的な問題
in four days
4日以内に
I'm afraid it will be too late
もう手遅れになるのではないかと思います
If you use autologous this
自己由来のものを使用する場合
cell words
細胞の言葉
words of limb cells
四肢細胞の言葉
you have to go through
あなたは通過しなければなりません
calculation,calculation,calculation
計算、計算、計算
Then also check that it is in the
次に、それが次の場所にあることも確認します。
The whole domination process has contamination
支配プロセス全体に汚染がある
this problem
この問題
this is a consideration
これは検討事項です
the second one is
2つ目は
If we use Algenic
アルジェニックを使用する場合
These cells are like the Japanese JGC day meeting company
この細胞は日本の日揮力海株式会社のようなものです
They're also doing this cell-forming
彼らはこの細胞形成も行っています
We use mass production
大量生産を採用しています
or edic
またはエディック
It should be a word back
言葉を返すはずだ
then stole it
それからそれを盗んだ
This is expected to learn from the material of cells
これは細胞の材質から学ぶことが期待される
or other different
または他の異なる
He's like this because he's also a drug dealer
彼は麻薬の売人でもあるからこうなのだ
I think these two considerations
この2点が考慮されると思います
I don't know what you think Mr. Xie
謝さんがどう思っているか分かりません。
I may not have explained clearly just now
今、明確に説明できていないかもしれませんが、
Our technology is grounded from the patient
私たちの技術は患者さんから生まれたものです
Whoever pulls the bone, kisses the water and pours it in
骨を引き抜いた者は誰でも、水にキスして注ぎます
The whole process takes about an hour and a half
全プロセスには約1時間半かかります
No need to culture cells, no need to move, no need
細胞を培養する必要がなく、移動する必要もありません。
So there's no need for those
だからそんなものは必要ない
So there is no such problem in time
だから時間的にはそんな問題ないよ
But if there is Alogenic, it is the issue
しかし、アロジェニックがあるなら、それが問題です
The issue is that people are the same
問題は人間は同じだということ
but not other animals
でも他の動物ではない
but different people
でも違う人
if we can
できれば
store all his cells
彼のすべての細胞を保存する
He will be available in the future
彼は将来利用できるようになるでしょう
This is of course a better way
もちろんこれはより良い方法です
Actually that's all
実はそれだけです
Biotech companies owned by pharmaceutical companies
製薬会社が所有するバイオテクノロジー企業
cell therapy companies their approach
細胞療法会社のアプローチ
Only in this way can we sell
このやり方でしか売れない
However, one must also consider that
ただし、次のことも考慮する必要があります
the same
同じ
Different Diseases Different Cells
さまざまな病気 さまざまな細胞
it has different pros and cons
それはさまざまな長所と短所があります
for example
例えば
Of course, what it does more often is stick to stem cells
もちろん、より頻繁に起こるのは幹細胞に付着することです
Stick to stem cells no matter where they come from
幹細胞がどこから来たのかに関係なく、幹細胞にこだわりましょう
Stick to stem cells it has great benefits
幹細胞にこだわると大きなメリットが得られます
It can be cultivated in large quantities
大量に栽培できる
You can move it and use it one by one
1つずつ移動して使用することもできます
It is also very organized
それも非常に組織化されています
Adhere to stem cells, there are many studies that say
幹細胞に付着するという多くの研究があります。
an immune response that does not produce too severe
重篤な症状を引き起こさない免疫反応
so it sounds like everything is fine
だからすべてがうまくいっているように聞こえる
But insisting on stem cells has its limits
しかし、幹細胞にこだわるのには限界がある
Because sticking to stem cells it mainly grows into bone
幹細胞にくっついて主に骨に成長するため
It is easier to grow into cartilage or fat cells
軟骨細胞や脂肪細胞に成長しやすくなります
to grow elsewhere
他の場所で成長する
That is to say, you need to rely on this to persist in stem cells
つまり、幹細胞で存続するにはこれに依存する必要があります。
become cardiomyocytes
心筋細胞になる
become nerve cells
神経細胞になる
Or maybe it's harder to become a liver cell
それとも肝細胞になるのが難しいのかもしれません
In fact, many people think that it is not
実はそうではない、と思っている人も多いのです
I even said that I knew it very early in the animal room
私は動物室の早い段階でそれを知っていたとさえ言いました
That is to say, you inject persistent stem cells into the heart
つまり、持続性幹細胞を心臓に注入します。
Although it can secrete
分泌できるのに
Growth factors grow blood vessels
成長因子は血管を成長させる
But he also grows bones
しかし骨も成長します
Then you want to inject stem cells into the heart to treat myocardial infarction
次に、心筋梗塞を治療するために幹細胞を心臓に注入したいと考えます。
Although he will grow blood vessels
血管は伸びるけど
but he has bones
でも彼には骨がある
You probably don't want to grow bones in your heart
おそらく、心に骨を生やしたくないのでしょう。
So actually every kind of
ですから実際にはあらゆる種類の
indication is still different
まだ表示が違う
problem must be considered
問題を考慮する必要がある
But in terms of part-time stem cells
しかしパートタイム幹細胞に関しては
He can be mass-bred out of the village
村から大量生産できる
he does have his great strengths
彼には大きな強みがある
Although we say
と言いながらも
Autologous does not need to consider the problem of immune rejection
自己由来は免疫拒絶の問題を考慮する必要がありません
And then pretty fast
それからかなり早く
but we also have our problems
しかし、私たちにも問題があります
For example very simple
たとえば非常にシンプルな
Many patients are
多くの患者さんは、
His bone marrow cells are not good
骨髄細胞の状態が良くない
It's just that his ability to grow blood vessels is not good.
ただ、血管を伸ばす能力が良くないのです。
He will have a myocardial infarction
彼は心筋梗塞を起こすだろう
what will happen
何が起こるか
Then you do it with his cells
それから、彼の細胞でそれをやってみましょう
Although we have given a good way
良い方法を提供しましたが、
I can't guarantee that he will have a good result.
彼が良い結果を出すかどうかは保証できない。
like we're doing animal experiments
動物実験をしているようなもの
Actually doing pig like this
実際にこんな感じで豚やってます
So these actually take some time
したがって、これらには実際には時間がかかります
to come and prove
来て証明する
which one will be better
どちらが良いでしょう
Better
より良い
But I think biomedical
しかし、私は生物医学的だと思います
Especially the progress of clinical medicine
特に臨床医学の進歩
Sometimes it takes a long time to develop
場合によっては開発に時間がかかることもある
Now for these results
さて、これらの結果について
Who will be the best in the future
将来誰が一番になるのか
It may take a while to understand
理解するまでに時間がかかるかもしれません
but you must do
しかし、あなたはしなければなりません
Otherwise these patients have no hope
そうでなければ、この患者たちに希望はない
no chance
チャンスは無い
And a patient with a heart attack
そして心臓発作を起こした患者
I probably didn't mention it just now.
おそらく今はそれについて言及しなかったと思います。
Although most of us in Taiwan
私たちのほとんどは台湾にいますが、
As long as it is a place above a medium-sized city
中規模都市以上の場所であれば
patients with myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞患者
Once sent to the emergency room
緊急治療室に送られたら
Can open blood vessels in 90 minutes
90分で血管を広げることができる
But don't forget to say
でも、言うことを忘れないでください
Myocardial infarction has about one-third of the patients
心筋梗塞患者の約3分の1
No chance of receiving these treatments at all
これらの治療を受ける可能性はまったくありません
it passes
それは通ります
Even a patient is lucky
患者でも幸運です
He can in the fastest time
彼は最速の時間でそれができる
Open up the blood vessels
血管を広げる
A day or two in an AC ward
エアコン病棟で1日か2日
transfer to general ward
一般病棟に転院
then went home
それから家に帰りました
Nearly one in five such patients
ほぼ5人に1人がそのような患者
Go home after these best treatments
最高の治療を受けたら帰宅できます
Three months back or new failure
3 か月前または新たな障害
Because he had a relatively large myocardial infarction
比較的大きな心筋梗塞を起こしていたため、
The moment of his heart attack had already sealed his fate
彼が心臓発作を起こした瞬間、すでに彼の運命は決まっていた
Some of these patients are quite young in their 30s and 40s.
患者さんの中には30代、40代という非常に若い方もいらっしゃいます。
But for the rest of his life, he spent decades in new exhaustion
しかし残りの人生において、彼は何十年も新たな疲労の中で過ごした
There are actually a lot of patients
非常に多くの患者
so one-fifth, almost one-fifth
5分の1、ほぼ5分の1
The whole world is the same, so is Taiwan
世界も同じ、台湾も同じ
There is currently no treatment for these patients
現在、これらの患者に対する治療法はありません
It's you, just give the strength agent, the cardiotonic agent
それはあなたです、強壮剤、強心剤を与えてください
Give the angiodysplasia agent this treatment
血管異形成の病原体にこの治療を施します
Patients with these treatments help
これらの治療を受けた患者は助かります
He's just delaying, just treating the symptoms.
彼は単に先送りしているだけで、対症療法を行っているだけです。
It doesn't really help his heart function much.
それは実際には彼の心臓の機能にはあまり役立ちません。
So in the end he still has to go until the heart grows bigger
結局のところ、彼は心が大きくなるまで行かなければなりません
to transplant this path
この道を移植するために
What we hope is to be able to help such patients
私たちはそんな患者様のお役に立てることを願っています
so these
それでこれら
What is being done now is to develop these technologies and these treatments
現在行われているのは、これらの技術と治療法の開発です。
In fact, many large parts
実は大きなパーツがたくさん
is here to help these
これらを助けるためにここにいます
I met the need to indication
指摘の必要性を満たした
including what we just
私たちが今していることも含めて
Talk about the next ischemic patient
次の虚血患者について話す
ok one last question
はい、最後に質問です
Ask Mr. Xie
謝さんに聞く
The Egyptian on the Chinese lion
中国のライオンに乗るエジプト人
The Egyptians made Aunt Mulan to take out the glandular organs for extra processing
エジプト人はムーランおばさんに追加の処理のために腺を摘出させた
There is no physiological meaning in it, except that they produce blood
血液を生成することを除いて、それには生理学的意味はありません。
This other eye problem is
このもう一つの目の問題は、
Some people judge that brain shit is death
脳のクソが死だと判断する人もいる
Some people say that the permanent stop of the glands is death
腺の永久的な停止は死であると言う人もいます
Are these two correlations related?
これら 2 つの相関関係は関連していますか?
The first question is easier for me to answer
最初の質問の方が答えやすいです
because i don't know sorry
分からないからごめんなさい
The second question we are judging
私たちが判断している2番目の質問
stop now, let's go
もうやめて、行きましょう
this is for sure
これは確かです
But the brain shit we are talking about is actually different from the vegetative state
しかし、私たちが話している脳のクソは実際には植物状態とは異なります
Brain shit means that if you don’t actively give him these life support systems
脳のクソってことは、あなたが積極的に生命維持装置を彼に提供しなければ、
he is going to pass
彼は通り過ぎるつもりです
Then our general vegetative people don’t need any respirator
そうすれば、私たちの一般的な植物人間は人工呼吸器を必要としません
without any drugs or anything
薬も何もなくても
he can still lie there
彼はまだそこに横たわることができる
So actually the two are not the same
したがって、実際にはこの2つは同じではありません
We're doing tracheal transplants for brain-dead patients.
私たちは脳死患者に対する気管移植を行っています。
not pointing fingers
指を指さないこと
is that clear? yes
それは明らかですか? はい
Just now you...
今、あなたは...
what is it
それは何ですか
The same factor makes the heart grow
同じ要素が心を成長させる
many reasons
多くの理由
But the most common is myocardial infarction
しかし、最も一般的なのは心筋梗塞です
Heart muscle grows for many reasons
心筋はさまざまな理由で成長します
myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞
slowly at most
せいぜいゆっくり
But there are many, many types of heart disease
しかし、心臓病には非常に多くの種類があります
This talk can last a long time
この話は長くなる可能性があります
no myocardial infarction
心筋梗塞はない
will, will
意志、意志
such as cardiomyopathy
心筋症などの
It has congenital defects in its muscles
先天的に筋肉に欠陥がある
Its heart will grow bigger and bigger
その心はどんどん大きくなっていきます
For example, after a long period of high blood pressure
たとえば、高血圧が長期間続いた後など、
The heart can compensate at first
最初は心臓が補うことができる
If it doesn't work later, it will collapse like this
後でダメならこのまま崩れるよ
Even a viral infection can give you cardiomyopathy
ウイルス感染でも心筋症になる可能性はある
It's not just closing arterial tissue and causing myocardial infarction.
動脈組織を閉鎖して心筋梗塞を引き起こすだけではありません。
Yes, so will demonic diseases
そうだ、悪魔の病気もそうなるだろう
But this is less
でもこれは少ないよ
not obsessive
執着的ではない
It's a problem with the demon
悪魔の問題だよ
give your heart a problem
心に問題を与えてください
This is now less and less
これも今では少なくなってきました
Because the most common access to this is the previous
これへの最も一般的なアクセスは前のものであるため、
caused by rheumatic fever
リウマチ熱が原因で起こる
When public health is poor
公衆衛生が悪いとき
For example, when you are twenty or thirty years old
たとえば、20歳、30歳のとき
Infectious rheumatic fever not well controlled
感染性リウマチ熱が十分にコントロールされていない
Slowly the companion demon becomes destructive
徐々に仲間の悪魔が破壊的になっていきます
After ten or twenty years, I will change my partner
10年後、20年後、パートナーを変える
This was very common in the past
昔はこういうのがよくあったよな
Thirty years ago we performed open heart surgery
30年前、私たちは開胸手術を行いました
Seventy to eighty percent are changing companions
7～8割が仲間を変えている
Now less than one out of ten is changing companions
現在、仲間を変える人は10人に1人未満です
It's all headhunting now
今はすべてヘッドハンティングです
not the same
不太一樣
exist
存在
that already has a companion
すでに仲間がいる
it will be like this
このようになります
Can't change eyes
目を変えることはできません
or already connected
またはすでに接続されています
want to change connection
接続を変更したい
it already has a companion
すでに仲間がいる
Everyone has a companion
誰にでも仲間がいる
There is no way without a companion
仲間がいないとどうしようもない
i keep saying that
私はそれを言い続けています
a lot of hair bits a lot a lot
髪の毛がたくさんある、たくさんある、たくさんある
but already have these
しかし、これらはすでに持っています
there is no ambulance
救急車はありません
If your normal life situation
通常の生活状況であれば、
or give a diuretic
または利尿剤を投与する
so that you can maintain a normal life
通常の生活を維持できるように
you can ignore him
彼を無視してもいいよ
but you have to always
でも常にそうしなければなりません
Follow up every three months
3か月ごとのフォローアップ
If your heart function starts to get worse
心臓の機能が悪化し始めたら
consider surgery
手術を検討する
That surgery usually we hope is
私たちが通常望んでいる手術は、
If you can repair it, try to repair it and don't replace it.
修理できる場合は、交換せずに修理してください。
Because the repair may only need two stitches.
修復は2針だけで済むかもしれないからです。
then if you change
それであなたが変わったら
the next question is
次の質問は
Then you want to change the pig half mill?
では、豚ハーフミルを変更したいですか？
half ground pork heart
豚ハツ半ひき肉
Your heart hair may need to be replaced with a metal half grinder
心臓の毛はメタルハーフグラインダーで交換する必要があるかもしれません
it has pros and cons
それは長所と短所があります
At this time, different factors should be considered
現時点では、さまざまな要素を考慮する必要があります
I'm basically saying
基本的に言ってるのは
Don't move the knife if you can
ナイフを使わなくても大丈夫ならナイフを使わないでください
It's you who rely on medication
薬に頼っているのはあなたです
There is no way to solve your problem
あなたの問題を解決する方法はありません
you are still uncomfortable
あなたはまだ不快です
If you're talking about
について話しているなら
your own situation
あなた自身の状況
Ninety percent of my judgment is yours
私の判断の90パーセントはあなたのものです
no knife needed
ナイフは必要ありません
Otherwise you wouldn't be like this
そうでなければこんな風にはならないよ
can talk to me like this for so long
こんなに長く私と話せますか
You're half dehydrated and there's a new noise
あなたは半分脱水状態で、新しい音が聞こえます
A new noise does not necessarily mean that there is a major problem
新しい異音は必ずしも大きな問題があることを意味するわけではありません
Might need
必要かもしれない
Make an appointment with Dr. Xie to visit National Taiwan University
謝博士と国立台湾大学を訪問する約束をする
I have an outpatient clinic at National Taiwan University Sina Surgery on Wednesday.
水曜日は国立台湾大学新浪外科の外来です。
I didn't have to see a hundred patients like the vice president said
副大統領が言ったように、100人の患者を診る必要はなかった
I suddenly won't have more than five patients
急に患者が5人を超えなくなりました
So you come and I can chat with you no problem
それで来てください、問題なくあなたとチャットできます
Periodic physical examination is still required
定期的な身体検査は引き続き必要です
well because of the time we have to be here
まあ、ここにいなければならない時間があるから
just stop
ただやめて
We thank Dr. Xie
謝博士に感謝します
Research continues to strengthen our future of this biomedical
研究はこの生物医学の将来を強化し続けています
Whether it's treating diseases, etc.
病気の治療などでも構いません。
we have great expectations thank you doctor
私たちは大きな期待を抱いています、ありがとう博士
Thank you for your viewing
ご視聴ありがとうございました